<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<FlavorTextDefs
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../data/Schema/FlavorText.xsd">
<!-- Created with the Gal Civ 3 Editor -->
<!-- Mercenaries_FlavorText.xml -->
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Rebirth_EndingFlavorText_Success</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>With the help of some new friends, the Torian Regime has been reborn. They have pushed the Drengin Empire out of their sector and built a strong base on which to rebuild.
The only question now is when, not will, the Drengin Empire counter attack?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Rebirth_EndingFlavorText_Failure</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>The Torian Regime has let its last chance for freedom slip from its hands. The victorious Drengin will now take the ultimate revenge for what they see as Torian insolence. It will not be long before the ancient Torian people will be nothing but a memory.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Envoys_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>My Lord, our ambassadors have concluded talks with the Arcean and Terran envoys. They have both agreed to help us in our revolution against the Drengin.
However, the Terran representative let us know that the priorities of their Commander Bradley require the bulk of their fleet elsewhere. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Envoys_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Have they offered us material help or just moral support?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Envoys_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>As long as they continue to harass the Drengin, we will consider that support enough.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Well sir, they have taken two Drengin colonies near the Drengin sector headquarters. Unfortunately they seem unwilling to move further into their space.
Their main fleet, as well as all T.A.S. Crusaders, are still involved in heavy fighting back near their homeworld of Earth.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Well, we will have to take what we can get. What of the Arceans?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>They have taken two Drengin colonies near the Drengin sector headquarters, but the bulk of their fleet has been pulled back to their home world. 
They seem to be planning something big. From what I gather, it might be a direct assault on Drengi.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent, if they move on Drengi, the Drengin will be very distracted. Any news on the Arceans?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR1-R1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Lord Verga of the Arceans was much more encouraging. They now have a new perspective on what it is to be enslaved by the Drengin. 
He has offered us an official alliance and promises to support us in the future. However, how much support is still in question, as they are currently putting their efforts into fortifying their territory.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR1-R1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Very well. With some luck, the Drengin will remain distracted long enough for us to do the same.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR2-R1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Lord Verga of the Arceans was much more encouraging. They now have a new perspective on what it is to be enslaved by the Drengin. 
He has offered an official alliance and promises to support us in the future. However, how much support is still in question, as they are currently putting their efforts into fortifying their territory.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_EnvoysR2-R1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Very well. With some luck, the Drengin will remain distracted long enough for us to do the same.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Warning_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Sir, our scouts have reported back. Most of the Drengin forces remaining in the area are retreating back to more secure territory.
They did find that the neighboring system of Blight still contains a Drengin Mining Colony. If we can capture it quickly, the Drengin will no longer have any means of support within lightyears of Toria.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Warning_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent, we will dispatch the Torian Liberation Fleet to secure the Blight system.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Warning_Counter1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Yes sir, but we will not be able to truly remove the Drengin presence until we have  some transports to take the planet.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Warning_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Unfortunately, we do not have any transport ships to secure the Blight system. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Warning_Counter2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Our Admirals tell us that the Liberation Fleet is at least capable of clearing the system of threats while we acquire the tools.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Greetings, Tlas Kzientha. We were very happy to see that you have been liberated from the Drengin yoke once again. Sadly my people have not been so lucky.
As you can see, we have been forced to find new ways to survive. However, this does put us in the position to be helpful to you.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>It is not surprising the Korx have found a way to survive. I assume you have also found a way to make a profit?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>You know us well. Even in these dark times, we have found a way to make a few credits.
We have gathered some of the most talented Mercenaries in the galaxy. We have convinced them that with the right representation they can make a better life for themselves, rather than being glorified pirates.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>This is fascinating but we have only recently retaken our home world and our resources are scarce to say the least.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Of course, of course. But still we could not help but notice your need for a transport. 
As a downtrodden victim of the Drengin, we would like to help. Anything that makes the Drengin pay is profit enough for us. At least for now.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered3_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>If you can provide us with a transport quickly, we will be in your debt!</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpIsOffered3_Counter1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>That's what we are counting on.

Just remember us when you need some additional muscle in your fleets. We have a wide variety of specializations. If you need it we probably have it. At least for a price.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_CaptureBlight_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We have taken Blight II, but it seems our Mercenary friend was a bit overly ambitious. Most of the planet's infrastructure has been lost.

What should we do with the surviving Drengin miners?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_CaptureBlight_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We must be better than our enemies. Take them into custody, but do not let any harm come to them. [COLOR=BenevolentBlue](Benevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_CaptureBlight_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Put them on the cheapest space-worthy bucket we can find, and point them toward Drengi. [COLOR=PragmaticGold](Pragmatic)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_CaptureBlight_Response3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Execute them. If they have not directly tormented our people, they encouraged it. [COLOR=WarRed](Malevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Congratulations on your victory on Blight II! We heard you were forced to resort to hiring a Mercenary transport to complete your goal. Be wary, the Korx are still as wily as ever. 
In the future we would like to make sure you can build your own transports, so we are sending you our [COLOR=UIDefaultHot]Planetary Invasion[/COLOR] Technology.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you very much. We will do our best to prove ourselves worthy of your kindness.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage1_Counter1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Any enemy of the Drengin is worthy of our support. 

Just make sure to point your new transport toward Drengi and we will be content.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, I have presented our agreement to the Arcean Assembly and they have signed off on our Alliance.
We were able to make it back to our territory with little harassment from the Drengin, but we did scan a large fleet that is still in the area. Be wary, that fleet alone is more than a match for our current forces.
</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you for the warning. We will be wary. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>In the meantime, we would like to establish an [COLOR=UIDefaultHot]Open Borders[/COLOR] treaty with you.
We must take advantage of the relative safety of the territory between our worlds. In fact, it might be a good time for us to establish a few trade routes between us. 
We will send you the coordinates of our capital, for when you are ready.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ArceanMessage3_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent, we will send a freighter over as soon as we feel it is safe.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Reminder_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha.
We just wanted to give you fair warning that we have been getting offers to hire several of our more destructive Mercenaries. Some of these have come from your ally, the Arceans. Others have been from the Drengin.
We will delay them as long as possible but we dare not openly defy the Drengin Empire at this point. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Reminder_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We understand. You must do what you need to survive. Thank you for the warning. [COLOR=BenevolentBlue](Benevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Reminder_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Delay them as long as you can.  We will do what we can to relieve you of your inventory problem as soon as possible. [COLOR=PragmaticGold](Pragmatic)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_Reminder_Response3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>You would work with the race that almost wiped out your species?</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ReminderR3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We do not wish to. Yet, the Korx are but a shadow of what we once were. If we anger our Mercenary Commanders and lose control of the Galactic Bazaar, we will have nothing.
And if the Drengin turn their full attention on us once again, we will certainly be utterly destroyed.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ReminderR3_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Do what you will. We will destroy any Mercenary that they use against us. [COLOR=WarRed](Malevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ReminderR3_Counter1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We would expect no less.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Congratulations once again on your victory over the Drengin Flagship. We have lost many noble warriors to that accursed dreadnought. This proves that our faith in the Torian people has not been misplaced. 
We would also like to thank you in a more practical way. Hopefully, this will help you further inconvenience the Drengin. [COLOR=UIDefaultHot]2500 Credits.[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We are only doing what we must in order to survive. But your help is always appreciated.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, while you were securing your territory, the Drengin flagship began attacking our forces. Apparently they do not appreciate our new alliance. 
We were able to defeat the accursed Dreadnought but we lost many brave warriors.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We are sorry for your losses. You have done the galaxy a great favor by eliminating that beast.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, good news! We defeated the Drengin Flagship. They were brazen enough to think they could push us out of the sector.
We hope that their defeat will prove helpful to your war effort.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestoyFlagShip3_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you for the assistance. You have done the galaxy a great favor eliminating that beast.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeBlessing_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>This planet is a blessing indeed. Not only have we been very lucky to find another Aquatic World so near our home system, it is also a very high class world.
Blessing II, is also promising, but we will need to research [COLOR=UIDefaultHot] Extreme World Colonization[/COLOR] to make it habitable. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeBlessing_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>An excellent suggestion, it will be very helpful to have a safe place to retreat in an emergency.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_MercNeedsHelp_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, we have received a distress call from one of our Mercenary Commanders. They seem to have run into difficulties and have become stranded on an uninhabited world on the other side of the black hole. 
If you were able to get a colony ship out there and give them some assistance, I am sure they would be willing to work for you as payment.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_MercNeedsHelp_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We will see what we can do.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyena_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>My Lord, we have located a Mercenary ship that has been marooned on this world for some time. They seem very happy to see us.
The bad news is that our colony commander is of the opinion that they were scouting the area for the Drengin before they crashed.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyena_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>I'm sure they have been punished enough. Assist them in repairs and see them off our planet. [COLOR=BenevolentBlue](Benevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyena_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tell them If they want off this planet they now serve the Torian Regime.[COLOR=PragmaticGold](Pragmatic)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyena_Response3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We will not tolerate anyone who works for the Drengin. Execute them and scrap their ship. [COLOR=WarRed](Malevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>My Lord, allow me to introduce myself, I am Reef Farseer, Commander of the Zindellit.
I understand we have you to thank for our rescue. I assure you we greatly regret ever taking that contract with the Drengin. I assure you we will not be any threat to the Torian Regime in the future.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>A valuable lesson to have learned indeed. For your sake, I hope we do not see you in Torian space again.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>My Lord, allow me to introduce myself, I am Reef Farseer, Commander of the Zindellit.
We thank you for the rescue and would be happy to pay off our debt by working for you. The Zindellit is a well armed and fast Survey Ship with an extremely long range.
It will take us a few weeks to complete repairs. We will report into your home world in a few weeks.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Your services will be very helpful. If you do well we may forget you ever worked for the Drengin.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR3_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>My lord. We have executed the Mercenary scoundrel Reed Farseer. This should send a message to the Bazaar about what happens to anyone that takes a contract against us.
His ship, the Zindellit, was very damaged. However, we were able to salvage some valuable gear.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_HelpedoutMercR3_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent, perhaps we will use the credits to hire a wiser mercenary.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_GetMerc_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, Reef Farseer is reporting in. The Zindellit is repaired and ready for departure. We have arrived in the Torian system and await your orders.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_GetMerc_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent, I'm sure we can find a good use for both you and your ship.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyce_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We are glad to see the Torian Regime growing. Now that you have a colony so close to our borders, it is more important than ever that we maintain good relations. 
Our scientists have asked me to offer you a [COLOR=UIDefaultHot] Technology Research Treaty[/COLOR], in the hopes that by sharing our knowledge, we will more efficiently resist the Drengin Empire.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyce_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent idea! Together we will greatly increase our research capacity. [COLOR=BenevolentBlue]Accept Research Treaty (Benevolent)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyce_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>What would be more helpful is if you could give us some of your existing technologies. [COLOR=PragmaticGold]Ask for techs (Pragmatic)[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyceR1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Excellent! if we can catch up to the technological level of the Drengin, our odds of defeating them once and for all will be much higher.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyceR1_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Agreed! </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyceR2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We understand that you are in a bind. Hopefully, we can find something that will help you out.
[COLOR=UIDefaultHot]2000 Research Points[/COLOR]</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeRoyceR2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Anything you can provide will be helpful.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TerranMessage_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, we have received a report from our remaining forces in your area that might prove very helpful to your people.
They have found an uncolonized Aquatic World on the edge of Drengin held territory. They think it would be a perfect beachhead to launch an invasion on their headquarters of Dark Sky.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TerranMessage_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you for the assistance. We will rally our forces immediately and secure the planet.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TerranMessage_Response2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you for the intel, unfortunately we are not ready to move that far in Drengin space. Yet.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeBlueOcean_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We are happy to see your war with the Drengin going well. While we still do not have any ships to spare, we have asked for volunteers from our local research staff. They have been dispatched to Blue Ocean with orders to help you with any research you need. [COLOR=UIDefaultHot]3000 Research Points[/COLOR] Technology.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_ColonizeBlueOcean_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Thank you very much, Commander Bradley. We will use them wisely.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TerranMessage2_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, we have just received grave news from our forces in your sector. 
Thinking to surprise the Drengin while your forces distracted them, they attempted a surprise attack on their local capital at Dark Sky.
They were utterly defeated. Apparently the Drengin have a powerful fleet protecting the planet.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TerranMessage2_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Grave news indeed. Thank you for the warning. Your fallen soldiers will be avenged.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyTorian_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Torian scum. You may have freed yourselves and the pathetic backwater of the galaxy you live in. But hear this; when we are done dealing with the Terran fleshlings, we will be back. All you have done is proven that you are not worth keeping around, no matter how tasty you are. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyTorian_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>If you return, we will be ready with our powerful new friends.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyArcean_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Torian scum. You may have convinced the Arceans to help you free yourselves and the pathetic backwater of the galaxy you live in. But hear this; when we are done dealing with the Terran fleshlings, we will be back. All you have done is proven that you are not worth keeping around, no matter how tasty you are. </Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyArcean_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>If you return, we will be ready. The Arceans are not our only friends.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyTerran_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Torian scum. You may have convinced the Terrans to help you free yourselves and the pathetic backwater of the galaxy you live in. But hear this; when we are done wiping the Terrans from existence, we will be back. All you have done is proven that you are not worth keeping around, no matter how tasty you are.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_TakeDarkSkyTerran_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>If you return, we will be ready. The Terrans are not our only friends.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestroytheDrengin_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>Tlas Kzientha, for a bunch of frogs, you have proven quite feisty. I regret not having you for a snack when I had the chance.
Enjoy your freedom. It will not last. The next time we meet we will not be so gentle.
</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
  <FlavorTextDef>
    <InternalName>Mercenaries_Rebirth_DestroytheDrengin_Response1_FlavorText</InternalName>
    <FlavorTextOption>
      <Text>We will be ready. That is, if you survive the Terran Crusade.</Text>
    </FlavorTextOption>
  </FlavorTextDef>
 
</FlavorTextDefs>
