<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<StringTableList
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schema/Lib/StringTable.xsd">
<!-- Created with the Gal Civ 3 Editor -->
<!-- TechDefsText.xml -->
 
<!-- Tech Names and Descriptions -->
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechTree_Name</Label>
    <String>Árvore genérica de tecnologia</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechTree_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Uma árvore tecnológica equilibrada.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonização</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de módulos de colônia e edifícios básicos de colônia.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Durante gerações a humanidade sonhou em colocar os pés em outros mundos. Esse sonho é agora uma realidade. Os pés estão sendo colocados em outros mundos. Estamos colocando muitas coisas em outros mundos de fato.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIndustrializationTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Industrialização</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIndustrializationTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de edifícios de colônia melhorados.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIndustrializationTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Tudo é mais difícil na superfície de um mundo alienígena, cada máquina que possuímos tem que ser ajustada para as diferenças de gravidade ou atmosfera, todas as nossas velhas constantes e atalhos empíricos têm que ser jogadas fora e reescritas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Especialização em fabricação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Não faz sentido parar na "competência básica" quando se trata de fazer coisas em ambientes alienígenas. Provavelmente deveríamos aprender com os muitos erros que ainda estamos cometendo, por exemplo, se apenas para melhorar nossa capacidade de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Especialização em pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossas fronteiras em rápida expansão disponibilizaram milhares e milhares de coisas novas para serem analisadas sob um microscópio. A expansão de nossas capacidades de pesquisa permitirá que nossos cientistas se mantenham atualizados.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Especialização industrial</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo de construção de centros de fabricação e pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Tendo descoberto o que funciona e não funciona em planetas alienígenas, fomos capazes de padronizar e modular um pouco nossas práticas de construção de edifícios, o que deve reduzir os custos de construção em toda a nossa civilização.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedConstruction_Name</Label>
    <String>Construção avançada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de fabricação avançada.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedConstruction_Dec</Label>
    <String>Os avanços nas ciências dos materiais nos deram as ferramentas para construirmos maiores e mais arrojados, para finalmente alcançarmos algumas das imaginações mais selvagens que nossos arquitetos nos propuseram.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Fabricação otimizada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Sempre que aumentamos a escala de nossa fabricação, também aumentamos a escala de nossos erros. É preciso tempo e esforço para eliminar esses erros, mas isso precisa ser feito se quisermos atingir nosso verdadeiro potencial de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Fabricação Eficiente</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Resistimos a deixar os contadores entrar nos centros de produção por muito tempo, porque o trabalho é perigoso e também porque ninguém gosta deles. Mas uma vez que eles encontraram uma maneira de entrar sorrateiramente, eles admitiram ter encontrado várias maneiras de reduzir os custos de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Fabricação sustentável</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz os custos de manutenção das plantas de manufatura.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>As fábricas e plantas de manufatura geram muitos subprodutos tóxicos que são caros de serem descartados. Ao tornar nossos processos de fabricação com menos desperdício, esperamos ver uma ampla economia de custos ao longo da vida útil de uma fábrica.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoManufacturingMethods_Name</Label>
    <String>Fabricação de precisão</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoManufacturingMethods_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de fabricação exótica.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoManufacturingMethods_Dec</Label>
    <String>Alguns de nossos processos de fabricação mais precisos resistiram à mudança para fora do mundo, lutando com a ampla gama de ambientes aos quais estão agora expostos. Pensamos tê-lo agora, mas ainda assim recomendamos que você invista em garantias estendidas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Indústria Militar</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de fabricação militar.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>O uso de ferramentas em nossos centros de fabricação para nos especializarmos na produção militar envia uma mensagem muito pouco amigável a qualquer pessoa que nos preste muita atenção. No entanto, isso deve fazer os meninos e meninas em fadigas de camuflagem adaptativas felizes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Indústria social</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de fabricação civil.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Um dos efeitos colaterais imprevistos da gestão de uma civilização nesta escala é encontrar coisas a ver com todas estas pessoas. Mantê-los felizes é tão importante quanto mantê-los seguros, e às vezes pode ser muito difícil para eles.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Fabricação competitiva</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz os custos de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Pensamos tirá-los de lá após a última vez, mas mais alguns contadores conseguiram entrar em nossos centros de fabricação. Ou eles estão vivendo agora nas paredes. Independentemente disso, eles encontraram mais algumas maneiras de reduzirmos nossas despesas gerais de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialExpertise_Name</Label>
    <String>Especialização industrial</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialExpertise_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção das mais modernas instalações de fabricação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialExpertise_Dec</Label>
    <String>Manipulando materiais a nível atômico, podemos agora construir coisas de precisão inigualável. Isto ampliou maciçamente nossa capacidade industrial, juntamente com a criação de uma classe inteiramente nova de questões de segurança no local de trabalho bastante aterrorizantes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Mestre da Montagem Militar</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Melhora a capacidade de fabricação militar.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Aos poucos, estamos descobrindo as últimas eficiências possíveis em nossos processos de fabricação militar, nossa civilização se transformando lentamente em uma máquina de guerra em si.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio da construção social</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves social manufacturing capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Poucos de nossos civis parecem se dar conta do desafio de construir as fazendas, hospitais e complexos de entretenimento dos quais eles dependem para sobreviver. E no entanto, toda vez que tentamos dizer-lhes o quanto estamos fazendo isso agora, eles apenas bocejam e vão embora.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPracticalFusion_Name</Label>
    <String>Fusão prática</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPracticalFusion_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de centrais elétricas melhoradas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPracticalFusion_Dec</Label>
    <String>Tornar os reatores de fusão em cascata robustos, à prova de adulterações e, em geral, à prova de catástrofes, exigiu muito trabalho. Mas agora que o fizemos, esperamos ver melhor capacidade de fabricação e apenas o mínimo de catástrofes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumPower_Name</Label>
    <String>Poder Quântico</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumPower_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de usinas de energia exóticas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumPower_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao aproveitar a energia quântica de ponto zero de um vácuo, nossos físicos afirmam que agora temos acesso a uma enorme fonte de energia. Não é infinito, mas o rapaz sempre existe muito dele.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingStimulus_Name</Label>
    <String>Estímulo à fabricação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingStimulus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumentam substancialmente os níveis de fabricação de nossa civilização por 15 turnos. (Capstone)</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingStimulus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao concentrar todas as nossas instalações de pesquisa no aumento da fabricação, seremos capazes de aumentar consideravelmente nossas capacidades de fabricação, pelo menos até que os pesquisadores comecem a reclamar de não terem permissão para fazer seus experimentos mais exóticos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInstitutionalResearch_Name</Label>
    <String>Pesquisa institucional</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInstitutionalResearch_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de pesquisa melhoradas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInstitutionalResearch_Dec</Label>
    <String>Estamos no nosso melhor quando não estamos apenas vivendo neste universo, mas observando-o. Descobrindo-o. Às vezes desmantelando pequenas partes dele. Ao criar lugares especiais para que isso aconteça, esperamos que os avanços da pesquisa ocorram com muito mais freqüência.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Pesquisa otimizada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a capacidade de pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Melhoramos e tornamos mais eficientes muitas de nossas práticas de pesquisa, o que deve levar a pesquisas mais rápidas ou, no mínimo, menos pesquisadores reclamando da burocracia.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Redução de custos de pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo de fabricação de melhorias na pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Com a pressa de começar a processar e analisar todos os novos dados que nossa rápida expansão proporcionou, uma série de práticas de pesquisa horrivelmente esbanjadoras tornou-se comum. Eliminando essas práticas, devemos ser capazes de tornar nossa pesquisa um pouco mais barata.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Pesquisa sustentável</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz os custos de manutenção de melhorias na pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Os laboratórios de pesquisa estão cheios de brinquedos caros que estão em um estado quase constante de avaria. Ao considerarmos como fazer parte disto de forma mais sustentável, esperamos ver uma ampla economia de custos ao longo da vida útil de um laboratório.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCenters_Name</Label>
    <String>Centros de pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCenters_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de pesquisa avançada.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCenters_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao colocar todas as nossas pessoas mais inteligentes e seus brinquedos favoritos no mesmo prédio, esperamos ver melhorias significativas em nossa capacidade de pesquisar novos campos. Além disso, lhes daremos comida para que não tenham motivos para sair.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Pesquisa focada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a capacidade de pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao concentrar nossos esforços em pesquisa pura, conseguimos obter uma melhoria significativa na taxa de novas descobertas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Foco na produção de pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo de melhorias na pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao concentrar nossos esforços em nossa infra-estrutura de pesquisa, conseguimos reduzir o custo de construção de novas instalações.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Economia da Pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz a manutenção de melhorias na pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ao focar como nossos pesquisadores trabalham e eliminar alguns dos experimentos mais esbanjadores, conseguimos reduzir significativamente a manutenção de nossas instalações de pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegratedResearch_Name</Label>
    <String>Pesquisa integrada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegratedResearch_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de pesquisa exóticas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegratedResearch_Dec</Label>
    <String>Fizemos grandes avanços em nossa compreensão do universo e agora precisamos de academias maiores para facilitar os estudos multidisciplinares necessários para empurrar o véu mais para trás. Os pesquisadores também estão exigindo algo chamado de "bar de faculdades".</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchMatrixTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Matriz de Pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchMatrixTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção das mais modernas instalações de pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchMatrixTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Imagine milhões de cientistas, trabalhando em uma instalação de pesquisa do tamanho de uma cidade, sem nenhuma das distrações do mundo exterior, como o clima ou o contato social básico. Sim, alguns se transformarão em psicopatas. Mas estávamos planejando ficar de olho neles de qualquer maneira.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeeperKnowledge_Name</Label>
    <String>Conhecimento profundo</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeeperKnowledge_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de pesquisa profunda.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeeperKnowledge_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa compreensão do universo tem crescido a passos largos. Equipes que fizeram um esforço para desacelerar e considerar algumas das implicações dessas descobertas estão agora revelando padrões mais profundos no tecido da realidade.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumUnderstanding_Name</Label>
    <String>Conhecimento quântico</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumUnderstanding_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de pesquisa profunda melhoradas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumUnderstanding_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossas últimas instalações não estão mais tateando às cegas no limite do mundo subatômico. Para começar, há vinte arestas, e são menos arestas que toroides, e agora, na verdade, há zero delas. Acontece que a realidade é super complicada.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeyondMortality_Name</Label>
    <String>Além da Mortalidade</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeyondMortality_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações avançadas de pesquisa profunda. Prepara a civilização para a Ascensão.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeyondMortality_Dec</Label>
    <String>A ascensão nos tornará imortais, e nos conduzirá a uma realidade que está além desta. O que lá está permanece um mistério, mas nunca nos afastamos deles antes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCoordination_Name</Label>
    <String>Coordenação de Pesquisa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCoordination_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações de apoio à pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchCoordination_Dec</Label>
    <String>A pesquisa coordenada só tem se tornado mais desafiadora à medida que nossa civilização tem crescido. Os Centros de Coordenação de Pesquisa devem ajudar a amenizar esse desafio, minimizando qualquer duplicação de esforços, e melhorar a produtividade das instalações de pesquisa vizinhas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNeroLinking_Name</Label>
    <String>Neuroligação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNeroLinking_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved research support facilities.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNeroLinking_Dec</Label>
    <String>Os benefícios da comunicação direta cérebro a cérebro serão sentidos em uma grande variedade de campos, mas considerando o quão incômodos socialmente muitos de nossos pesquisadores são, suspeitamos que eles serão os que mais lucrarão em viver em um mundo sem conversa fiada.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryImprovement_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetologia</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryImprovement_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de edifícios civis. Aumenta o crescimento populacional.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryImprovement_Dec</Label>
    <String>Metade da diversão de mudar-se para um novo lugar é consertá-lo de acordo com suas necessidades. Isso é mais difícil quando o novo lugar é todo um planeta alienígena, mas finalmente estamos desenvolvendo as ferramentas e técnicas para fazer exatamente isso.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Melhoria do solo</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa tecnologia agrícola melhorou drasticamente e, como resultado, estamos começando a ver um aumento no rendimento das colheitas. As cenouras ainda têm aquele gosto estranho, mas estamos trabalhando para isso.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Crescimento Acelerado</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta o crescimento populacional.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Agora que somos capazes de modular os efeitos que um mundo estranho tem sobre a fertilidade, nossas taxas de crescimento populacional estão começando a subir. Mais bebês por enquanto, mas mais trabalhadores em breve.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Produção aperfeiçoada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a produção.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Não estamos mais apenas sobrevivendo em novos mundos, mas prosperando lá. Graças ao melhor rendimento em nutrientes e técnicas de preservação, nossos trabalhadores podem trabalhar mais e mais, melhorando a capacidade de produção de toda a nossa civilização.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoAgriculturalAdaptation_Name</Label>
    <String>Adaptação agrícola</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoAgriculturalAdaptation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de fazendas melhoradas. Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoAgriculturalAdaptation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Adaptar nossa experiência agrícola para se adaptar a uma variedade de ambientes estranhos provou ser um desafio, e levou muitos avanços simultâneos em nosso entendimento do solo, da ciência atmosférica e das pás. É isso mesmo. Em alguns planetas, precisamos de pás especiais.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultura Acelerada</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Adapting our planting, feeding, and harvesting regimens to account for differences in the seasons of alien worlds takes a lot of effort and has to be fine tuned on every planet. But now that we're able to do it, we expect to see greater food yields.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultura Eficiente</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo das fazendas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Agora que temos mais experiência no cultivo de alimentos em mundos alienígenas, nossos engenheiros agrícolas são capazes de prever com antecedência o equipamento agrícola que uma colônia precisará antes de ser formada, levando a custos mais baixos para o início das operações.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultura Sustentável</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz o custo de manutenção das fazendas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Dando um passo atrás na vanguarda da ciência agrícola, e utilizando equipamentos mais antigos e mais confiáveis, podemos reduzir os custos de funcionamento da maioria de nossas fazendas..</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntensiveFarming_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultura Intensiva</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntensiveFarming_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de fazendas avançadas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntensiveFarming_Dec</Label>
    <String>A maximização da produção alimentar de um determinado terreno de solo é um passo caro, mas muito necessário para aqueles mundos onde a terra arável vem com um prêmio.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Foco Nutricional</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Os micróbios presentes em solo alienígena reagem de forma diferente aos nutrientes do que estamos acostumados, e é preciso algum tempo para afinar nossas técnicas de fertilização para manter nossas próprias plantas alimentadas. Mas agora que o fizemos, esperamos ver uma produção alimentar ainda maior.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Foco na adaptabilidade da fazenda</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of farms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Por fim, nos debruçamos sobre as espécies e cepas de plantas que se adaptam à mais ampla gama de ambientes. Ao concentrar nossos esforços de produção nessas culturas, os custos de arranque de qualquer fazenda devem agora ser muito mais gerenciáveis.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Foco na gestão da fazenda</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduz os custos de manutenção das fazendas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Os agricultores de toda a nossa civilização estão enfrentando desafios agrícolas únicos todos os dias. Ao implementar sistemas de compartilhamento de informações em toda a civilização, podemos difundir ainda mais nossas melhores práticas, reduzindo os custos operacionais agrícolas em todos os lugares.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessFarming_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultura sem perda</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessFarming_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de fazendas exóticas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessFarming_Dec</Label>
    <String>As melhorias em nossos sistemas de reciclagem e distribuição de nutrientes levaram a fazendas quase perfeitamente eficientes. Nossos fazendeiros não precisam nem sujar as mãos agora e estão ficando um pouco preocupados com isso.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Mestres Agricultores</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa capacidade de produção de alimentos deu mais um passo à frente. Além disso, finalmente tiramos aquele gosto estranho das cenouras, mas acontece que agora todos gostam, então tivemos que colocá-lo de volta.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Abundância</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>As fazendas aumentam o crescimento populacional.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Temos uma quantidade tão excessiva de alimentos agora que muitos de nosso povo tomaram quase como um desafio criar famílias capazes de consumir tudo isso.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFoodDistributionTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Distribuição de alimentos</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFoodDistributionTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de edifícios de apoio à agricultura. Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFoodDistributionTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Parece entediante, e na verdade também é entediante, mas graças aos avanços na xeno-contabilidade e a melhoria resultante na logística de nosso sistema de distribuição de alimentos, estamos agora economizando muitos alimentos que antes tinham sido desperdiçados.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIrrigation_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Irrigação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIrrigation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de edifícios melhorados de apoio à agricultura. Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoIrrigation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Há uma série de desafios surpreendentes ao irrigar um planeta alienígena, devido à incrível variedade de condições gravitacionais, do solo e da atmosfera que encontramos. Além disso, a água está, em muitos casos, escondida.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiomassResequencing_Name</Label>
    <String>Resequenciamento de Biomassa</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiomassResequencing_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de edifícios avançados de apoio à agricultura. Aumenta a produção de alimentos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiomassResequencing_Dec</Label>
    <String>Fundamentalmente, os alimentos são pouco mais que longas cadeias de carbono dispostas em moléculas que achamos digeríveis e saborosas. Plantas e animais têm feito um bom trabalho de sequenciamento dessas cadeias até hoje, mas não está na hora de deixarmos um robô abrir uma fenda?</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoBiology_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Biologia</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoBiology_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações médicas melhoradas. Aumenta o crescimento populacional.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoBiology_Dec</Label>
    <String>Compreender como os seres humanos se adaptam ao ambiente microbiológico de mundos alienígenas será fundamental para nossas chances de sobrevivência quando colonizarmos as estrelas. Perder uma colônia para uma diarréia catastrófica simplesmente não é uma opção.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationEnhancement_Name</Label>
    <String>Melhoria da População</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced medical facilities. Increases population growth.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationEnhancement_Dec</Label>
    <String>É preciso muito romance, mas para que nossas colônias tenham sucesso, elas precisam de bebês, e precisam deles rapidamente. Dedicar mais recursos para melhorar a fertilidade e a música de humor deve ajudar.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBioReplication_Name</Label>
    <String>Bio-replicação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBioReplication_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de instalações médicas exóticas. Aumenta o crescimento populacional.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBioReplication_Dec</Label>
    <String>Uma vez que tiramos todas as partes divertidas da reprodução, fomos capazes de aumentar drasticamente nossas taxas de crescimento. Claro, a bio-replicação pode estar nos levando a um mundo de pesadelo de conformismo e menos vagas de estacionamento disponíveis. Mas vamos conseguir de alguma forma.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalEngineering_Name</Label>
    <String>Engenharia Ambiental</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalEngineering_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a melhoria do solo e melhora os efeitos do terreno adjacente.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalEngineering_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa capacidade de melhorar e melhorar o ambiente em que trabalhamos trará benefícios a quase todos os aspectos da colonização e tornará os passeios ao ar livre um pouco menos mortais.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExtremeWorldColonization_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonização Extrema</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExtremeWorldColonization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a instalação em mundos extremos, com potencial de produção reduzido.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExtremeWorldColonization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Não estamos mais limitados aos frutos de baixo peso do estoque de planetas da galáxia. Não será uma vida fácil para ninguém que vive nestes novos mundos, mas será uma vida.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio do mundo aquático</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Normalizes Production of Aquatic Worlds, and boost their wealth and Tourism.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa experiência lidando com os desafios da vida no mundo aquático nos permitiu tornar a vida lá quase tão confortável quanto em qualquer outro lugar de nossa civilização. Os bonés de banho não são mais obrigatórios.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio do Mundo Congelado</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Normaliza a Produção de Mundos Congelados, e aumenta sua Pesquisa e Influência.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Agora somos tão bons em viver em mundos de bola de neve que muitos colonos passam dias sem usar luvas, algo que teria sido considerado imprudente mesmo há alguns anos atrás.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio do Mundo Árido</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Normaliza a Produção de Mundos Áridos, e impulsiona sua Produção e Militares.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Foi necessária alguma tecnologia de reciclagem de água cara e maciçamente invasiva para fazê-lo, mas a vida em mundos áridos é agora mais ou menos tão produtiva quanto em qualquer outro lugar. Os cateteres agora também são muito mais confortáveis.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAtmosphericCleansing_Name</Label>
    <String>Limpeza Atmosférica</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAtmosphericCleansing_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a instalação em mundos radioativos e tóxicos, com potencial de produção reduzido.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAtmosphericCleansing_Dec</Label>
    <String>Mesmo os ambientes planetários mais sujos e tóxicos podem agora ser colonizados por nós. Boa sorte para os pobres bastardos que vão em busca disso, mas ao menos agora terão uma chance de lutar.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection1_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio do mundo radioativo</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Normaliza a Produção de Mundos Radioativos, e aumenta sua produção de Produção.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection1_Dec</Label>
    <String>As mutações e defeitos genéticos que eram um fato da vida dos primeiros colonizadores de mundos radioativos são agora coisa do passado. Quaisquer outras mutações serão deixadas em vigor apenas para fins cosméticos.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection2_Name</Label>
    <String>Domínio do Mundo Tóxico</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Normaliza a Produção de Mundos Tóxicos, e aumenta sua produção de Pesquisa.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Temos dominado os desafios de viver até mesmo nos planetas mais venenosos. Você ainda não vai querer ir para fora sem seu capacete, mas nós mudamos a maioria dos lugares que valem a pena ir para dentro de qualquer maneira.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTerraformingTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Terraformação</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTerraformingTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite a construção de plantas de terraformação.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTerraformingTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>A terraformação é um negócio complicado, delicadamente posicionado entre tornar um mundo mais habitável para nós sem destruir toda a sua biosfera para fazê-lo. E não há nada para fazer.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHabitatImprovement_Name</Label>
    <String>Melhoria do habitat</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHabitatImprovement_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced terraforming plants.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHabitatImprovement_Dec</Label>
    <String>Nossa capacidade de manipular a biosfera melhorou ao ponto de podermos tratar continentes inteiros com uma tela. Vamos pintar um retrato de uma civilização pujante e próspera? Ou o equivalente a escrever nossos nomes na neve com urina?</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSoilReclamation_Name</Label>
    <String>Reclamação do solo</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSoilReclamation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Permite o uso de terrenos quase inúteis.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSoilReclamation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Muitos planetas fazem um trabalho muito pobre de tornar o terreno utilizável para fins coloniais. Onde a natureza deixou cair a bola, nós entramos, e agora somos capazes de desenvolver o que antes eram locais muito marginais.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalResequencing_Name</Label>
    <String>Resequenciamento ambiental</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalResequencing_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Aumenta a quantidade de terra utilizável em todos os planetas colonizados.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnvironmentalResequencing_Dec</Label>
    <String>Agora estamos jogando com forças poderosas, capazes de manipular o terreno planetário em uma escala nunca vista antes. Devemos ter certeza de usar este poder com sabedoria, ou pelo menos não ativamente para o mal.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEngineeringTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Engineering</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEngineeringTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of hyperdrives and tiny hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEngineeringTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>For generations, we've looked up at the stars and wondered, "What if?" Well buckle up, because "if" has happened. By bending space around our ships we can use conventional propulsion in a pocket of normal space while accelerating at incredible speeds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTravel_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Travel</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTravel_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves sensor, life support, and speed of all ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTravel_Dec</Label>
    <String>Even at the incredible speeds we can travel at now, if we want to journey anywhere beyond the closest stars we'll need to make significant improvements to our navigational and life support systems. More refined hyperdrives wouldn't hurt either.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Hyperdrive Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the speed of all ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>After analyzing how our first generation of hyperdrives have (and haven't) worked, we've come up with a number of ways to improve our ships' speeds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Transportation Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the Mass of Colony &amp; Constuctor modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Pushing large Support Modules through space is inherently wasteful, by miniaturizing and optimizing the larger components, we can fit more on a ship, allowing them to go farther and faster than ever.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Advanced Recirculation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the range of all ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>After listening to the complaints and coughs of our returning crews, we've improved the life support recirculation systems of our ships, which should marginally increase their effective range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonDriveTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Ion Drive</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonDriveTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the construction of improved hyperdrives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonDriveTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>By using magnetic fields to capture ions from the interstellar medium during hyperdrive flight, we can funnel this additional mass into the exhaust of our engines, increasing our overall speed. Called Ion Drives, they make us go faster, basically.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>High Output Drives</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the speed of all ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The ion capture technology of our Ion Drives requires a fiendish amount of tuning that our ship's engineers are only just learning to automate. Once this work is done, we should see slightly higher speeds across our fleet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Drive Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the cost of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Hyperfield generators are no longer the rare pieces of equipment they once were, and we're beginning to see efficiencies of scale that have reduced the unit-cost for each one.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Drive Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the mass of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Every year our hyperdrives get more efficient and smaller. Less room for the engines means more room for everything else, benefiting every type of ship we could conceive of.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldTheory_Name</Label>
    <String>Warp Field Theory</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldTheory_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the construction of advanced hyperdrives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldTheory_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our researchers are now able to "stack" up the space-bending fields of our hyperdrives, magnifying their acceleration effect. They call these stacked arrangements "Warp Fields" and are now using them to create vastly more powerful engines.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Warp Field Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the speed of all ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By tuning the arrangement of stacked hyperfields in a variety of dimensions, we've found some surprisingly cheap ways to improve the speed of our Warp Drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Field Generator Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the cost of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Now that we're using stacked fields and multi-field generators, even the most minuscule improvement in cost-efficiency can lead to significant savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Field Generator Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the mass of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>With a bit of experience working with the effects of stacked hyperfields, we've determined that we were stacking them inefficiently. Smaller field generators can achieve the same effects as their fatter predecessors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpWaves_Name</Label>
    <String>Hyperwarp Waves</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpWaves_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the construction of exotic hyperdrives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpWaves_Dec</Label>
    <String>Hyperwarp Waves consist of warp fields cascading in front of the vessel, allowing a warp drive to effectively compress already compressed space. That glosses over a number of complicated mathematical issues, but the end result is even faster drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Drive Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the cost of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>No other civilization in the galaxy can match ours for the ease and efficiency with which we build our drives. And still human ingenuity can find ways to make them cheaper.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Drive Mass Reduction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the mass of drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have all but mastered hyperfield technology, and are now capable of wringing the most possible speed from even the smallest engines.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFoldingTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Stellar Folding</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFoldingTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate hyperdrives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFoldingTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Stellar folding bends space on a scale never seen before, hyperfields approaching the diameter of a star. Our ships are now the fastest in the galaxy, and perhaps the fastest the galaxy has ever seen.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldProjection_Name</Label>
    <String>Hyperfield Projection</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldProjection_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of speed boosting support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldProjection_Dec</Label>
    <String>Careful analysis of the way hyperfield waves interact when ships are travelling in formation has revealed the possibility of building larger field generators capable of increasing the drive efficiency of an entire fleet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravityFieldManipulation_Name</Label>
    <String>Gravity Field Manipulation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravityFieldManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced speed boosting support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravityFieldManipulation_Dec</Label>
    <String>It took a long time to finally find the graviton. It turned out to be inside us the whole time. But now we can use it to generate massive artificial gravity fields, which should improve the maneuverability and tactical options of our ships in combat.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldDisruption_Name</Label>
    <String>Hyperfield Disruption</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldDisruption_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of enemy speed reduction modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperfieldDisruption_Dec</Label>
    <String>By analyzing the interference effects of multiple hyperwave fields from different ships travelling in close proximity, we can now limit the speed of enemy ships within the range of a properly equipped starbase.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFieldProjection_Name</Label>
    <String>Stellar Field Projection</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFieldProjection_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced speed boosting support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarFieldProjection_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Stellar Field Projector allows properly equipped ships to effectively "tow" ships with less capable drives. The same technology will help us improve the hyperfield enhancing capabilities of our support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDriveOptimization._Name</Label>
    <String>Drive System Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDriveOptimization._ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Substantially boost the speed of all ships for 15 Turns. (Capstone)</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDriveOptimization._Dec</Label>
    <String>With a little persuasion we have been able to convince many of our researchers leave there cozy research centers and do some practical studies, onboard our ships.  The result has been an impressive increase of our average ship speeds. Unfortunate the researchers will need to return to there offices before to long, unless we continue to fund this endeavor.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSurvey_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Survey</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSurvey_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved sensors and survey modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSurvey_Dec</Label>
    <String>"Look before you leap," is excellent advice in all sorts of aspects of life and galactic civilization building. Now we finally have the sensor and survey tools for our ships to do just that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Amplification</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases sensor range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The latest generation of nano-processors allow us to more rapidly process the massive volumes of information our sensors return, improving the overall effectiveness of our sensor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensors Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The hyperfield detectors which our sensors use were originally cobbled together from left over drives. Now that we have dedicated sensor manufacturing equipment, we can expect to see some significant cost savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our earliest sensors were crude, jury-rigged things, and if we begin swapping out their parts for dedicated sensor-specific equipment, we should see significant weight savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldSensors_Name</Label>
    <String>Energy Field Sensors</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldSensors_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldSensors_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improvements in our understanding of the effects of space folding have revealed that hyperdrives are detectable at much greater distances than previously believed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Field Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases sensor range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our technicians have found that by turning one of the knobs up, our sensor systems can see a bit further. We feel kind of dumb for not realizing this before.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Efficacy Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our sensor systems had several redundant parts, which when stripped out has led to the production of cheaper, more efficient systems. The accountants are all very excited.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Sensors</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>The creation of high-density field detection components should lead to more compact sensors, leaving our ship designers more room to install guns. Everyone wins. Except the people the guns are pointed at.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSubspaceSensors_Name</Label>
    <String>Subspace Sensors</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSubspaceSensors_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSubspaceSensors_Dec</Label>
    <String>Subspace is the 12-dimension space that lies at right angles to and a little bit behind our universe, and it took us a very long time to figure out how to look at it. The upshot is that we can now build a new generation of very powerful sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Simplification</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>When a ragtag group of science-accountants teamed up with the goal of identifying cost savings in our most advanced sensor systems, few believed they had a chance. Many openly mocked them. Some people spit on them. But somehow they managed it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Mass Reduction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>A careful analysis of our newest sensor systems has revealed that several of their components don't technically have to exist in this universe. By shifting their workload into another plane, we can reduce the amount of mass we have to lug around in ours.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingAssistTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Targeting Assist</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingAssistTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of targeting and stealth modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingAssistTech_Dec</Label>
    <String> A study of how our ships have performed in combat has led to a number of improvements in our tactical targeting systems. At the same time, we've devised a system which should confuse enemy sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingSupport_Name</Label>
    <String>Targeting Support</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingSupport_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of targeting and evasion modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTargetingSupport_Dec</Label>
    <String> We've adapted our tactical sensor improvements into support modules, capable of allowing a single ship to provide sensor accuracy and evasive benefits to an entire fleet of vessels.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoArcheology_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Archeology</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoArcheology_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor research, and begins the path towards Ascension.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoArcheology_Dec</Label>
    <String>For some time we've known of a race, or races, of long dead aliens called the Precursors. It's taken some time to adapt our survey systems to identify their relics, but now that we have, we hope to learn a few of their secrets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorStudies_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Studies</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorStudies_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor research and Ascension crystal mining.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorStudies_Dec</Label>
    <String>Now that we've had an opportunity to study a few precursor relics, we've been able to detect patterns in them which have allowed us to build a framework which should greatly aid future Precursor research efforts.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Technologist</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor relic research benefits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Understanding Precursor artifacts involves throwing out many of our pre-conceived notions about technology. Their interfaces don't just assume we have different anatomy; they assume we have different ways of thinking entirely.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Cultural Studies</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor relic cultural benefits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The public seems fascinated by the Precursors, and the relics we've found have had a surprising effect on our society. We can now try to capitalize on these cultural benefits. Souvenirs. Wacky catchphrases. Things like that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Capitalization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor relic economic benefits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Most of the Precursor relics we find are  a mystery to us, doing little more than generating patterns of pretty lights. Though it turns out there is a massive consumer market for pretty lights which we might want to capitalize on.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorExploitation_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Exploitation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorExploitation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor research and Ascension crystal mining.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorExploitation_Dec</Label>
    <String>The study of Precursor relics requires very specialized equipment. The construction of dedicated facilities staffed with Precursor specialists will allow us to make the most of these incredible artifacts.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorEngineering_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Engineering</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorEngineering_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor research and Ascension crystal mining.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorEngineering_Dec</Label>
    <String>We're now able to try recreating some of the Precursor's technology. Extremely advanced fabrication equipment will be needed to continue this work, but the benefits to our other research programs could be immeasurable.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorUnderstanding_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Understanding</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorUnderstanding_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Precursor research. Prepares civilization for Ascension.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorUnderstanding_Dec</Label>
    <String>Precursor relics reveal their secrets to us with ease now, and we're close to building our own relics ourselves. We have almost as full an understanding of Precursor technology as the Precursors did themselves.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupport_Name</Label>
    <String>Life Support</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupport_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupport_Dec</Label>
    <String>It seems surprising that the factor limiting the travel range for our ships is its life support system, but there you have it. For anything less than a colony ship, keeping the occupants alive is now a bigger challenge than keeping the engines fueled.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Improved Life Support</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases ship range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our experience with the rigors of space travel, and the shrieked radio transmissions of the few who fell to the rigors of space travel, have revealed a number of small improvements we might be able to make to our existing life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Life Support Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Reducing the cost of building life support systems is one of those things we often have to do that we don't want to advertise too much. It's hard enough finding naval recruits as it is.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Life Support Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By minimizing the amount of weight and space our life support systems take up, we leave more room for our life reduction systems, which is what we're now calling guns.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldGeneration_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Field Generation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldGeneration_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldGeneration_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our growing familiarity with force fields has enabled us to replace our mechanical life support systems with more elegant field based processors. Food is now stored in a single block of nutrient-rich sludge, piped directly into the user's mouth.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Range Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases ship range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By aerating the nutrient sludge we provide our crews it takes up significantly more volume in their stomachs, making them feel full with less food. There are some associated problems with, uh, gas, but we're coming up with special filters to address that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Manufacturing Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our life support systems are now really, really cheap. Still effective though, let's not forget that. Maybe let's not even call them cheap. "Economical," or "Value," maybe.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Support Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By using the latest generation of efficient field generators, and also putting our crews on a diet, we've been able to reduce the mass of our life support systems even more.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPromethionSupportSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Promethion Support Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPromethionSupportSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPromethionSupportSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Promethion Support System extends our field life support further, with all the requirements for a living organism - oxygen, water, and food - now piped directly into that organism rather than left to float around and get on the equipment.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Support System Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Some of the crews are finding out how little we're spending on their life support systems. "Do you think we're worthless?" they shout. And we don't, we really don't. They're not worthless at all! Worth less, yes. But that's different.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Mass Reduction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces life support mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our nutrient sludge now delivers itself to the crew using embedded Promethion field effectors, saving us the weight of carrying around heavy fixed effectors. The embedded effectors come out in the waste stream, ready for reuse. After cleaning, of course.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessSupportSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Lossless Support Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessSupportSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessSupportSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our life support systems are now close to perfect, wasting no resources whatsoever and recycling essentially all waste products. As an added bonus, the fields have been reduced in size and are now much less humiliating for the crew.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Field Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of fleet life support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our switch to field based life support systems has made it possible to offload some materials to other vessels. Additionally, it should now be possible to supplement fleets via unmanned supply probes launched from an appropriately equipped facility.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExplorationExtention_Name</Label>
    <String>Exploration Extension</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExplorationExtention_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced fleet life support modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericExplorationExtention_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've adapted the latest in Promethion support field technology to be used by our fleet-support vessels, thus increasing an entire fleet's travel range. Additionally, we've made significant improvements to our starbase life support extension modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalManufacturing_Name</Label>
    <String>Orbital Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalManufacturing_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved manufacturing buildings, and small hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalManufacturing_Dec</Label>
    <String>Moving our ship construction operations to micro-gravity environments will eventually allow for the construction of massive structures. We're not quite there yet, but the first step out of the well was always going to be the biggest.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Skilled Starship Construction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Shipyard manufacturing.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>You can't put just anyone in a space suit and get them to build things in orbit. It turns out that most people don't understand what an orbit is. Some improved training programs should dramatically improve our orbital manufacturing capability.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Improved Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Getting material to the right orbit at the right time is something we're only just coming to grips with. It turns out that orbital plane change maneuvers are really expensive. But once we scale this up, our logistical ability should greatly improve.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Storage Maximization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Ironically enough, space is at a premium in space, inside of our hulls at least. Even small improvements in packing efficiencies are worth the effort of hunting them down.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityConstruction_Name</Label>
    <String>Zero Gravity Construction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of medium hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityConstruction_Dec</Label>
    <String>Most of our initial attempts at micro-gravity construction used clumsy variations of ground-based techniques, not far removed from banging rocks together. Now that we have a little more experience, we should be able to build on a much larger scale.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Reinforcement</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull hit points.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>After donating a few hulls for weapons practice, we were able to see the structural damage inflicted on them, and identify structural reinforcements that should toughen each ship substantially.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Shipyard Efficiency</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Worksite planning in an orbital environment is a seriously complicated business, but now that we've got the hang of it, we should see significant cost savings for every hull we construct.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Capacity Hulls</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We're now able to build hollow structural elements still capable of handling very high compression loads. By maximizing the use of these and routing various ancillary ship systems through the cavities, we can save space for mission critical equipment.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLargeScaleConstruction_Name</Label>
    <String>Large Scale Construction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLargeScaleConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of large hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLargeScaleConstruction_Dec</Label>
    <String>Building larger hulls is more involved than just adding more stuff to them. Ensuring that they won't collapse under acceleration is a serious challenge. Seating, to ensure our crews doesn't collapse under acceleration is another surprising challenge.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Hardened Hulls</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull hit points.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>It seems counter-intuitive, but by introducing very small weaknesses in the molecular structure of our hulls, we can make them deformable in controlled ways, making our hulls quite a bit more resilient.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Starship Manufacturing Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>The latest generation of self-propelled manufacturing equipment will allow our workers to maneuver inside of hulls with much greater ease, reducing the challenge and expense of construction.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Capacity Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>As our hulls grew ever larger, we began to lose some of the art of packing that our predecessors had. But now thanks to the scale of our ships, even very small improvements in packing can lead to more room for everything else.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassiveScaleConstruction_Name</Label>
    <String>Massive Scale Construction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassiveScaleConstruction_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of huge hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassiveScaleConstruction_Dec</Label>
    <String>We're building massive ships capable of blotting out the stars. Obviously any ship can blot out the stars if you get close enough to it. You just don't have to get very close to these ones for that to be the case. Nor would you want to.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Shipwrights</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>That we build the best ships in the galaxy is undeniable, but that we do it so economically is what's really impressive. Our enemies have never been menaced so thriftily.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Maximization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases hull capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Thanks to advances in the field of bristling, never before have our ships been so bristling with weapons. They could also bristle with other things we suppose. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullStrengthening_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Strengthening</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullStrengthening_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of tougher hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullStrengthening_Dec</Label>
    <String> Using new force field technologies, we've been able to embed strengthening fields within the structures of our vessels, making them substantially more resistant to damage. They also now tingle if you lick them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullRepairSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Repair Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullRepairSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of hull support and repair modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullRepairSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String> The same field technology we use to strengthen our ships can now be used to conduct partial repairs as well, straightening and reinforcing battle-damaged structural elements.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSelfHealingHulls_Name</Label>
    <String>Self Healing Hulls</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSelfHealingHulls_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of tactical repair modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSelfHealingHulls_Dec</Label>
    <String>Tiny little self-replicating nanobots are capable of almost anything as long as we don't ask too many questions about them. Nanobot repair modules in our ships and starbases will be able to repair damage during battle itself.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Carriers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of carrier modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Carrier combat will allow us to project force while keeping our capital ships out of danger. Fighters are a lot more replaceable and there's no shortage of volunteers to fly them. Apparently there's something glamorous about dying in a very small ship.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Interceptor Drones</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows for the construction of cheap and light Interceptor Drones</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>These little drones are fast and deadly, and more importantly cheap. They also have the added advantage of not requiring a crew, which saves lives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Guardian Drones</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String> Allows for the construction of cheap and light Guardian Drones.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>These tuff little drones will guard our Support and Capital ships to the end, and when they are destroyed, no lives are lost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighCapacityCarriers_Name</Label>
    <String>High Capacity Carriers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighCapacityCarriers_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of high capacity carrier modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighCapacityCarriers_Dec</Label>
    <String> Thanks to our latest generation of fighters, designed to be more compact and packable, and the improved repair, reloading, and recovery facilities that go with them, we're now able to deploy high-capacity carriers.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarLogistics_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarLogistics_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of mining facilities. Increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarLogistics_Dec</Label>
    <String>It's one thing to build a ship, it's another thing to keep it running. None of this is exciting of course. Logistics officers are some of the most boring people you're ever likely to meet. But a necessary evil.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Advanced Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Now that we've figured out some of the issues relativistic travel creates with our timekeeping and administration, we've been able to significantly improve our logistical capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Output Mining</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases mining production.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>An asteroid mining operation is a ballet of activity, as boring machines, ore haulers, and repair drones swarm about an asteroid. Keeping these pieces moving is challenging, and improving the organization is a sure way to improve its output.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Sustainable Shipyards</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces Shipyard decay rate.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Shipyards are, by some measures, the most complicated constructs humanity has ever created. Any improvement we can make to the management and operation of these beasts will result in significant cost savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFleetLogisticsTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Fleet Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFleetLogisticsTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Greatly increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFleetLogisticsTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Scaling up our naval operations to include large multi-vessel fleets has created a number of additional logistical challenges which we're only just now coming to grips with. We'll definitely stop sending ships out without oxygen now though.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeepSpaceLogistics_Name</Label>
    <String>Deep Space Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeepSpaceLogistics_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Greatly increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDeepSpaceLogistics_Dec</Label>
    <String>Whether it's via unmanned probes, deep space caches, or our network of merchant vessels, keeping our fleets well stocked while our civilization expands has proven to be a tremendous, but still very boring, challenge.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticLogistics_Name</Label>
    <String>Galactic Logistics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticLogistics_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Greatly increases Logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticLogistics_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our mastery of mass-scale logistics is the envy of the galaxy. Well. The part of the galaxy which gets excited about logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarMining_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Mining</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarMining_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of mining facilities.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarMining_Dec</Label>
    <String>We can't have ships without the resources to build them. The same can be said for lots of things actually. Improved mining technologies will benefit every aspect of our civilization. At least the aspects of our civilization which require building things.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEfficiencyMining_Name</Label>
    <String>High Efficiency Mining</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEfficiencyMining_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved mining facilities.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEfficiencyMining_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our mining operations are capable of generating more resources while losing less miners than ever before. The miners rejoice! Well. Not rejoice, exactly. They seem less grumpy than usual. Still, that's something.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResourceExtraction_Name</Label>
    <String>Resource Extraction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResourceExtraction_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced mining facilities.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResourceExtraction_Dec</Label>
    <String>Valuable resources can be found in most asteroids in extremely low concentrations. Extracting these hasn't been practical until the development of probes capable of independently navigating the subsurface to collect the goodies within.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessMining_Name</Label>
    <String>Lossless Mining</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessMining_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of targeted resource extractor modules.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLosslessMining_Dec</Label>
    <String>Miniaturizing our resource extraction probes to the nano-scale has allowed for almost perfectly lossless resource extraction. Additionally, the rarest of rare resources can now feasibly be targeted for extraction.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarfareTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Warfare</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarfareTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows research of weapons technologies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarfareTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>We can't be naive about who or what we might find in the galaxy. From this point on, our ships must be armed, whether to protect against a yet unseen enemy, or even ourselves.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSystemsTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Weapons Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSystemsTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic weapon systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSystemsTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The best defense is a good offense. Interestingly, so is the best offense. With that in mind, we've developed weapon systems which should prove very well suited to space-based defense. And, as discussed, offense.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech1_Name</Label>
    <String>Targeting Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the Accuracy of all weapon systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have increased the targeting systems of our existing weapons substantially, and what we have learned will apply to future weapons systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech2_Name</Label>
    <String>Miniaturization Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the Mass of all weapons systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have reduced the mass of our existing weapons systems, and what we have learned will apply to future weapons as well.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech3_Name</Label>
    <String>Production Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces the Cost of all weapons systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecializationTech3_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have reduced the cost of our existing weapons systems, and what we have learned will apply to future weapons as well.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeapons_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeapons_Dec</Label>
    <String>Whether light, particles, or both at the same time, there's an awful lot of destructive potential in suddenly sending a lot of it all at one place.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Focused Beam Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases damage of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>A new generation of the ultra transparent materials we use in our focusing crystals has made it possible to increase the damage output of our beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low-Cost Beam Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Beam weapons will never be cheap, but some economies of scale have led to price reductions in the magnification and focusing equipment these weapons rely upon.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Weapons Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Lacking the requirements for ammunition storage, beam weapons have always been mass-efficient. And after some hard work by the boys and girls in the lab, now they're a bit more so.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMatterDisruption_Name</Label>
    <String>Matter Disruption</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMatterDisruption_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMatterDisruption_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our researchers have been able to weaponize a collimated beam of particles capable of disrupting the strong nuclear force, severing the bonds which hold the nucleus together, turning matter into smaller chunks of matter.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Amplification</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases damage of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Advances in crystallography have created a new generation of focusing crystals capable of handling much greater quantities of energy without fracturing. All of our beam weapons just got a little bit badder.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Manufacturing Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Manufacturing beam weapons is as much art as science, requiring highly trained technicians to individually tune each weapon. But if we can standardize this a bit, and even automate portions of it, we should be able to reduce the cost of each unit.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Beam Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>The heaviest parts of beam weapons have always been the charge coils and their associated cooling equipment. But with the latest generation of super-conductors we can now build these smaller and more compact than ever.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlasmaProjection_Name</Label>
    <String>Plasma Projection</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlasmaProjection_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlasmaProjection_Dec</Label>
    <String>We're now able to generate collimated plasma containment fields at incredible distances. The upshot to this is that we can now send massive quantities of plasma at relativistic velocities in the direction of anything we don't like very much.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Beam Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our supply chain for the creation of plasma containment fields had a couple of kinks that needed to get worked out, but now that we have, we expect to be able to create beam weapons for far cheaper.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Beam Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We're now able to push our beam weapons right up to the energy density limits that physics allow. If we want any more power per unit of mass, we may have to move to a different universe.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyPhasing_Name</Label>
    <String>Energy Phasing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyPhasing_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of devastating beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyPhasing_Dec</Label>
    <String>The phaser particle is almost impossible to understand if you don't have several advanced degrees and possibly an extra brain. In short, these particles can induce a chain reaction that breaks an enemy down into neutrinos, effectively evaporating it. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDoomRayTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Doom Ray</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDoomRayTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDoomRayTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>An adaptation of the phaser particle emitter has resulted in massive improvements in the induced matter-breakdown reaction. Also of note, our scientists are pretty sure the reaction won't consume the entire universe. So that's good news.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponAugmentation_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Weapon Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of beam support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponAugmentation_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've found that the capacity of our beam energy storage systems can be augmented by an external field, which allows for increased beam output. Such fields could be projected at a distance, improving the beam output of an entire fleet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyTransfer_Name</Label>
    <String>High Energy Transfer</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyTransfer_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved beam support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyTransfer_Dec</Label>
    <String>After considerable study in the way that beam weapons interact on a subatomic level with both shield systems and hulls, we've developed systems capable of reducing the effectiveness of enemy shields or absorbing enemy beam attacks on our own vessels.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyMagnification_Name</Label>
    <String>High Energy Magnification</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyMagnification_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced beam support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyMagnification_Dec</Label>
    <String>An improved understanding of the effects our beam augmentation fields have has resulted in the possibility of even greater beam outputs. Additionally, we can now build beams that can cripple enemy shields.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileWeapons_Name</Label>
    <String>Missile Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileWeapons_Dec</Label>
    <String>Conceptually simple, though there's no shame in that, missile-based weapons provide a tremendous amount of punch for their cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Rapid Fire Missiles</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases firing speed of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our weapons engineers have determined that shooting more missiles at things makes them blow up faster. Which seems obvious in retrospect. Anyways, our missile launchers shoot more now.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Cost Missiles</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Missiles were always going to be the most cost-effective means of making things hurt, and now they're a little bit more so.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Missile Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Reviews of training data and engagement encounters reveals one overriding request from the field. "We want more missiles. Give us more missiles." Well, having reduced the mass of our launchers and ammunition racks, we're now able to do just that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHarpoonTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Harpoons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHarpoonTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHarpoonTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Harpoon class of missiles employ a number of improvements in speed, range, tracking, and warhead yield, resulting in our most powerful conventional missile system yet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Warhead Acceleration</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases range of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>More target drones have given their lives for our glory, and a careful analysis of their deaths has revealed some exciting possibilities in the field of shaped charges, which should improve the destructive yield of our warheads.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Warhead Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The most delicate part of missile manufacturing was the warhead, for obvious reasons. But the latest generation of ultra-stable explosives should reduce both manufacturing costs and workplace accidents significantly.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Warheads</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By using the latest generation of shaped-charge warheads to reduce the weight of each individual missile, with no corresponding loss of destructive power, we can make room for more missile launchers in total.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonicWarheads_Name</Label>
    <String>Photonic Warheads</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonicWarheads_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonicWarheads_Dec</Label>
    <String>By embedding a device in our warheads which releases a high energy burst of photons at the moment of impact, we can achieve substantial penetration against both armor and shield systems, greatly increasing the destructive potential of our warheads.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Missile Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our missile manufacturing facilities are now almost perfectly efficient, wasting no material whatsoever. Destruction shouldn't come so cheap, yet here we are.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Warheads</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>A new field based guidance system which uses forcefields to provide final maneuvering capabilities should cut down on the weight of our missiles systems a bit more.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonTorpedos_Name</Label>
    <String>Photon Torpedoes</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonTorpedos_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of devastating missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPhotonTorpedos_Dec</Label>
    <String>By matching a wide-spectrum version of the photon-encasement armor piercing technology with our latest anti-matter warheads, we've created a weapon with truly colossal damage potential. They glow a new color too.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNightmareTorpedoTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Nightmare Torpedoes</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNightmareTorpedoTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericNightmareTorpedoTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The Nightmare torpedo contains a tiny singularity trapped in a pocket universe, which upon being released causes horrifying damage to anything foolish enough to be standing by a place we're firing something called Nightmare Torpedoes at.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileAugmentation_Name</Label>
    <String>Missile Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of missile support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileAugmentation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our weapons researchers have come up with a number of ship and starbase modules which can improve the tracking and ultimately the range of our missiles.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedMissileGuidance_Name</Label>
    <String>Advanced Missile Guidance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedMissileGuidance_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved missile support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedMissileGuidance_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improved decoy and camouflage systems will greatly increase the survivability of our missiles when faced with point defenses. And our missile support modules now feature a number of predictive systems which should help missile range even more.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntelligentWarheads_Name</Label>
    <String>Intelligent Warheads</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntelligentWarheads_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced missile support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntelligentWarheads_Dec</Label>
    <String>Cluster warheads are capable of specifically targeting and neutralizing enemy point defense systems. And our missile support systems can now make use of information-sharing "pilot" missiles, which allow for more efficient guidance and improved range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticWeapons_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Weapons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticWeapons_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticWeapons_Dec</Label>
    <String>There's just something nice and honest about a projectile, isn't there? And thanks to a little help from teams of massive electromagnets, we've now got some extremely fast projectiles to work with.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Range Extension</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases range of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>A switch to slightly smaller projectiles, along with improved energy delivery systems, has led to significant improvements in the speed of each projectile, and thus the effective range of each unit.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Weapon Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Never before have we needed to make electromagnetic coils in such quantity, and the early days of kinetic weapons were plagued by supply problems. But that's finally been addressed, and we should see cost savings across all of our kinetic weapon programs.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Some experiments with the winding patterns of our electromagnetic coils has revealed a number of subtle synergistic effects which we can take advantage of, leading to tighter, more compact coils, and ultimately, lower mass weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPulseCannonTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Pulse Cannons</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPulseCannonTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPulseCannonTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Tight clusters of particles emitted at high velocity gets around some of the practical limitations of slug based mass drivers. These pulse cannons have similar tactical characteristics as previous kinetic weapons. They're just more powerful.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Frictionless Acceleration</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases range of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our newest superconductors and the steeper energy delivery curves they enable should lead to higher muzzle velocities, at the trade off of smaller projectiles. These weapons should have a longer effective range with no reduction in damage potential.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Cost Accelerators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The latest generation of superconducting electromagnetic coils and their less-strenuous cooling requirements make them much less fragile to handle. We expect to see significant cost savings now that we won't break as many during production.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Accelerators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our new ultra-low resistance electromagnets generate a lot more kick per unit weight, leading to lower mass accelerators. We can feel free to cram more of them into whatever we're cramming them in to.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitonThrower_Name</Label>
    <String>Graviton Thrower</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitonThrower_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitonThrower_Dec</Label>
    <String>By launching pulses of gravitons we can induce massive shifts in the local gravity of enemy ships that they strike. This will cause incredible amounts of damage, and probably make anyone standing nearby feel really dizzy right before they die.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Accelerator Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>"We Make Kinetic Weapons Faster," is probably the dumbest slogan ever conceived of, but the factory workers seem really proud of it, so no-one had the heart to tell them. And to be fair, they do make them really quite quickly and cheaply now.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Accelerators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our scientists have all but mastered kinetic weapons, having made them as mass efficient as theoretically possible, allowing even our smallest vessels to pack a hellacious punch.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumDrivers_Name</Label>
    <String>Quantum Drivers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumDrivers_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of devastating kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericQuantumDrivers_Dec</Label>
    <String>Quantum drivers fire shells that contain small quantum fields which pull in a tremendous amount of mass from a neighboring dimension on impact. We're not sure which dimension. We can only hope that they didn't need that mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSingularityDrivers_Name</Label>
    <String>Singularity Drivers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSingularityDrivers_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSingularityDrivers_Dec</Label>
    <String>The pinnacle of kinetic weapon technology, these launch micro singularities that collapse into existence shortly after impact. These are bad news, the worst news really, for anyone who can't get out of the way.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAugmentation_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of kinetic support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAugmentation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Inertial dampening should be impossible in this universe, which is why we were a little surprised we were able to pull it off. We've used this stroke of luck to create systems which can boost the velocity and effective range of our kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassManipulation_Name</Label>
    <String>Mass Manipulation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved kinetic support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMassManipulation_Dec</Label>
    <String>We can now embed inertial modification tech inside projectiles, allowing them to generate ultra-dense outer surfaces for a brief period to improve their armor penetrating capabilities. And our kinetic augmentation systems have gotten a bit better.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInertialMagnification_Name</Label>
    <String>Inertial Magnification</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInertialMagnification_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced kinetic support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInertialMagnification_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our projectiles are now capable of attacking armor directly, creating low density fissures that can cause the whole structure to splinter. Additionally our kinetic augmentation systems have  increased their range boosting effects yet again.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMilitarizationTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Militarization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMilitarizationTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the construction of military shipyards and defense platforms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMilitarizationTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>We already have a significant amount of structures in orbit and on the ground, all of which can be militarized with modest extra investment and some new uniforms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryInvasion_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetary Invasion</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryInvasion_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows transport modules to be constructed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetaryInvasion_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've developed the equipment and tactics necessary to land on a world and take it by force. A little hard to imagine it, but we must accept that humans are now the alien invaders.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetary Bombardment</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows Planetary Bombardments to be conducted during invasions.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String> So it turns out that thanks to the properties of mass, the easiest way to pacify something is to just drop something on it. It takes a bit of practice to get right, but the practice is fun itself.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Information Warfare</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows Informational Warfare tactics to be used during invasions.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Information warfare lacks a certain visceral appeal. But EMPs and targeted hacking attacks can cripple an enemy's coordination and limit the effectiveness of their defenses without needing to risk any of our own viscera.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Biological Warfare</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows Biological Warfare tactics to be used during invasions.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Let's be honest. If we're now the alien invaders, there's no reason we have to pretend we're the good guys. Yes we'll have to live with the consequences of using biological weapons. But at least we'll be the ones who live.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStallerMarines_Name</Label>
    <String>Stellar Marines</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStallerMarines_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves soldier effectiveness and transport capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStallerMarines_Dec</Label>
    <String> A greater understanding of the tactics and training required for effective ground-based combat has led to a new form of military unit which specializes in establishing beachheads in unfriendly gravity wells.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Tidal Disruption</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows tidal disruption tactics to be used during invasions.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String> By directing powerful gravitational fields at enemy ground defenses, we can induce flooding and even tectonic activity. The ground shall quake beneath our enemy's feet or feet-analogs.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Core Detonation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows core detonation tactics to be used during invasions.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String> Inducing a planet to suddenly experience massive, worldwide volcanic activity is a pretty extreme step. That said, it certainly will pacify any hostiles. Also liquefy them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSoldiers_Name</Label>
    <String>Drone Soldiers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSoldiers_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves soldier effectiveness and transport capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSoldiers_Dec</Label>
    <String> There are massive benefits in unit reliability and coordination if our troops are programmed to unfailingly do what we tell them to. And we won't have to feel so bad about losing these ones.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedInvasionTactics_Name</Label>
    <String>Advanced Invasion Tactics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedInvasionTactics_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Improves soldier effectiveness and allows construction of advanced transports.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAdvancedInvasionTactics_Dec</Label>
    <String> A new generation of invasion transports, along with a new generation of soldiers that don't mind being stacked like firewood, allows us to put boots on the ground faster than ever.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefenseSystemTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Defense Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefenseSystemTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic defensive systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefenseSystemTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Naval crews are notoriously squishy, and otherwise difficult to protect in a ship that operates in hard vacuum. But we've got to do something, or they're going to stop getting in the ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of shields.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Deflecting or diffusing incoming weapon fire is really, really hard, and we're far from having a really good understanding of it. Our latest round of research has only succeeded in making existing shield systems a bit cheaper to build.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of point defenses.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Making our point defenses fire more crap into the space around the ship is a simple solution to a complicated question. Though still a surprisingly effective one.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces mass of armor.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By adjusting the size and positioning of our armor panels, we've been able to minimize overlap and other inefficiencies, and can now provide the same level of protection to our ships for less overall weight.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>No longer must our ships cower behind crude deflector fields. The latest generation of shields, although expensive, are capable of stopping incoming attacks outright, rather than just deflecting or diffusing their impact.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Enhancement</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases shield strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Of all the suggestions we've received from the field on how to improve our shield systems, "Please make them bigger," seemed to be the most popular. So we've done that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Cost Shield Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We probably shouldn't talk in front of the troops about our efforts to make our shield systems cheaper, even if it means more shields to go around for everyone. Because that's not how they'll see it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>The first few generation of field emitters used in our shield systems were incredibly bulky and cumbersome. And they still are, frankly. Just a bit less so now.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierFieldGeneration_Name</Label>
    <String>Barrier Field Generation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierFieldGeneration_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierFieldGeneration_Dec</Label>
    <String>The latest generation of shields, the so-called Barrier Field, is capable of absorbing a portion of the energy which strikes it. This dramatically increases the energy efficiency of the system, allowing for ultimately much more powerful shields.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>High Output Shield Generators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases shield strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>The first generation of energy absorbers in our Barrier Field systems used a model of capacitor which occasionally exploded violently. Crews had decidedly mixed feelings about this, so we replaced those capacitors with a slightly more robust model.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Cost Shield Generators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Since the first few shield emitters went out the door, we've slowly been able to achieve some economies of scale in the manufacture of these systems, reducing the cost of all future installations.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Shield Generators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've recently been able to shave a ton of weight off of our shield generators thanks to the latest generation of superconductors and their less extensive cooling requirements.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericForceFieldTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Force Fields</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericForceFieldTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericForceFieldTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The latest generation of shields are capable of directing vast amounts of additional energy to a specific section of shields within nanoseconds of the moment of impact, allowing for shields which are much stronger relative to their respective weight.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Shield Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Cheaper shields never meant less effective shields, and it's only taken a few decades for our crews to finally understand that. Which is good, because our shields are spectacularly cheap now.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Shield Generators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces shield mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>It's impossible to make the energy emitters of our shields any denser our engineers claim. They claim that kind of thing a lot and always take it back later, but they seem pretty sure this time.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvulnerabilityTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Invulnerability</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvulnerabilityTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvulnerabilityTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>"Invulnerable" may be a bit of an exaggeration. Our researchers allow that some theoretical weapons could penetrate these shields. But those would be some pretty terrifying weapons, and even then you'd rather be behind this shield than not.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSupportSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Support Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSupportSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of shield support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldSupportSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>Advances in the focusing capabilities of our shield generators has given us the ability to generate and augment the shields of friendly ships. This should provide massive tactical and strategic options for fleet operations.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldAugmentation_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved shield support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldAugmentation_Dec</Label>
    <String>The same technology we've used to generate shields at a distance can now be done with our Barrier Field systems, allowing for even greater improvements in fleet survivability.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldManipulation_Name</Label>
    <String>Energy Field Manipulation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced shield support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldManipulation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our mastery of the energy fields needed to create and maintain shields has resulted in a couple interesting new technologies, capable of interfering with enemy shield systems, or massively shielding friendly units within range.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenses_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defenses</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenses_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenses_Dec</Label>
    <String>Arrays of tiny computer controlled railguns that track and destroy incoming missiles are unparalleled at protecting ships and starbases from missile attacks, though they still aren't terribly helpful at defending against other classes of weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Smart Point Defenses</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases point defense strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>A careful analysis of various missile performance envelopes has led us to adjust the firing patterns of our point defense systems, making them a bit more effective.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Cost Point Defenses</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>The sensor equipment our point defense systems use is fairly specialized equipment that was initially quite rare and costly. Now that we're building a lot of point defenses, the price of those systems is starting to come down.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>The slugs fired by point defenses don't need to be large, and were limited by the fact that we couldn't build railguns any smaller. But now that we can build more compact units, we should see significant weight savings for all our point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasures_Name</Label>
    <String>Counter Measures</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasures_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasures_Dec</Label>
    <String>By deploying electronic counter measures which interfere with and confuse incoming missile attacks, we've greatly increased the survivability of our ships and starbases. Against missiles at least. Still hard to confuse a laser.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Adaptive Counter Measures</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases point defense strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>There's always a generational game of leap frog being played between missile designers and ECM designers, but we believe our latest algorithms have given us the leg up on the bad guys this time.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Counter Measure Manufacturing</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our earliest attempts at ECM suites were heavily customizable, requiring a great deal of hand tuning to make them perform at their best. Now that we know what works, we can automate much more of the manufacturing and installation process.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Low Mass Counter Measures</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our first ECM suites were cobbled together from a half dozen different processors and transmitters. We've since streamlined those into a single unit which weighs much less.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSentrySystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Drone Sentry Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSentrySystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSentrySystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>By installing our point defense systems on drone platforms that orbit our ships at a distance, we can add a valuable extra layer of protection against missile attacks.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Point Defense Assembly</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>To be fair, only a few of our drone systems have ever actually shot each other in combat situations. But by minimizing that just a little bit more, we should be able to make our point defenses a little more cost-effective, if a bit less funny.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Point Defenses</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces point defense mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Once we realized point defense drones don't need much personal space, we were able to start packing them in a lot tighter.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArreonMissileDefenseTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Aereon Missile Defense</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArreonMissileDefenseTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArreonMissileDefenseTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The ultimate in point defense technology, featuring the latest generation of micro-drones armed with railguns, ECM and smart chafe. Aereon systems fill the space around a ship with a cloud of debris so thick no enemy missiles are likely to survive.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseSupportSystem_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Support</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseSupportSystem_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of point defense support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseSupportSystem_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our experience working with small scale point defenses has led to a type of long range missile tracking system which should enhance the point defense capabilities of an entire fleet.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseAugmentation_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Augmentation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseAugmentation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved point defense support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseAugmentation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Wide area missile disruptors enhance the effectiveness of our existing counter measures, adding a much needed layer of extra missile security to our fleets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseManipulation_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Manipulation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseManipulation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced point defense support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseManipulation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Fleet-wide drone systems will provide massive missile security to an entire fleet. Additionally we can now equip point defense disruptors, essentially a type of counter-counter-measure, which should boost the effectiveness of our own missile attacks.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>A big lump of ultra-dense material remains an effective, if unsubtle, method of protection from modern space-based weaponry. Subtlety is overrated though.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Reinforced Armor</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases armor strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>A simple mistake by one of our fabricators resulted in a set of armor panels marginally denser and more resilient than we'd seen before. It took us a long time to replicate that mistake, but now that we have, our ships should be a little tougher to kill.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Low-Cost Armor</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>One of the biggest challenges with armor manufacturing was simply the logistics of moving rare and heavy resources and materials around. Now that we've got our supply chain sorted out, we can expect to see some nice cost savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Miniaturization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By its very nature, armor is always going to be a fairly mass-intensive means of protection. That said, we can do a few things to improve the precision and fit of armor plating, which should cut down on weight a bit.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDurantiumCompositeTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Durantium Composite</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDurantiumCompositeTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDurantiumCompositeTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Certain materials, when stacked in specific arrangements have a synergistic effect on the strength of their neighbors under compressive forces. We call these new composites Durantium, and they should tremendously increase the survivability of our ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Lamination</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases armor strength.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>A careful study of battle-damaged ships has revealed previously unknown weaknesses in our armor systems. Basically, we know why some of them were cracking in half now. We'll do something about that right away.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Manufacturing Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>If our crews ask, it's not that our armor is cheap. It's that we've found a more efficient way of manufacturing it. But yes, it is pretty cheap.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Mass Reduction</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Some experiments with the arrangement of our Durantium composites has revealed that we can get away with slightly less dense materials at certain layers with no impact to the armor's effectiveness.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKanviumLaminateTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Kanvium Laminate</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKanviumLaminateTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKanviumLaminateTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Kanvium armor uses a new type of lamination which causes surrounding materials to partially fluidize on impact, deforming in a recoverable way. Impacts are spread out over a much larger area, then flow back into its original shape.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>Master Armorers</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor cost.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>With modern armoring systems, the design of the armor informs the shape of the ship as much as the other way around. Properly armoring a ship involves a complicated series of trade offs, which when we get right, mean ships protected for much cheaper.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>High Density Armor</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces armor mass.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>On a weight basis, our armor systems are now as efficient as they can possibly be, 99.3% of all total installed mass dedicated to offensive energy absorption or dispersion. That's really, really good the researchers promise.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroPointArmorTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Zero Point Armor</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroPointArmorTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroPointArmorTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have a hard time proving zero point armor even exists, only knowing of it by the effect it has. It appears to tap into the zero-point energy of the quantum vacuum to repulse incoming energy. It's almost impossibly tough, we can prove that much.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSupportSystems_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Support Systems</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSupportSystems_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of armor support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorSupportSystems_Dec</Label>
    <String>In the factory, we've begun producing armor plating with a variety of force field based technologies. By adapting these fields into ship modules, we can create a hardening effect at a distance, making every ship in a fleet substantially more durable.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorEnhancement_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Enhancement</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorEnhancement_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved armor support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorEnhancement_Dec</Label>
    <String>The fields that we use to generate hardening effects have twenty seven different "poles" which can be cycled through, changing the alignment of the hardening effects in the affected material, generating substantially stronger, more resilient materials.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegrityFieldProjection_Name</Label>
    <String>Integrity Field Projection</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegrityFieldProjection_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced armor support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIntegrityFieldProjection_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our latest generation of armoring fields no longer just generate hardening effects at a distance, but can induce material fluidization and shape recovery. These new Integrity Fields can make our fleets invulnerable to all but the most powerful attacks.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommunicationsTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Governance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommunicationsTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows research of communications technologies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommunicationsTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've already seen glimpses of evidence that we're not alone in this galaxy. Which presents an incredible danger, but also, perhaps, an opportunity. But also, let's stress again, danger.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTranslatorTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Universal Translator</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTranslatorTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Can begin communicating with aliens. Boosts diplomacy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTranslatorTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Intense study of the fragments of alien text and speech has allowed us to create a Universal Translator that will let us communicate with any new races we come across.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Diplomatic Reasoning</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Diplomacy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We've begun simulating different rhetorical and diplomatic approaches when dealing with aliens, revealing several ways we might improve their attitudes towards us. Our role-playing has enabled us to talk prettier, essentially.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Influential Voice</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our culture has a way of communicating what our diplomats cannot. By increasing the ease with which other civilizations can access our culture we can win hearts and minds before we even get to the negotiating table.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Efficient Administrators</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases the number of Administrators your Civilization can support. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>As our Civilization grows, we find ourselves needing more and more Administrators to oversee our far flung Starbases.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarGovernance_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Governance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarGovernance_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Stellar Empire form of government, and increases our Administrative capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarGovernance_Dec</Label>
    <String>Governing a civilization on this scale parallels our experience exploring our own world hundreds of years ago. A history we'd better refamiliarize ourselves with quickly, before we get any space tea dumped in our harbors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Federalist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Federalist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Federalist parties advocate a relatively weak central government that offloads much of its responsibility to lower, more local governmental groups. This bias towards local regulation seems to encourage economic development.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Populist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Populist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Populist forms of government are designed to make people happy, even at the cost of economic strength. As a side-effect of this relentless interest in pleasing others, Populist governments are often very good at diplomacy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Universalist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Universalist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Universalist governments attempt to be all things to all people. That can be a lot of people, none of whom ever seem to agree on anything, but a balanced approach like this at least ensures a government has no weak spots.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticGovernance_Name</Label>
    <String>Galactic Governance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticGovernance_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Galactic Republic form of government, and increases our Administrative capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticGovernance_Dec</Label>
    <String>By granting limited powers of self rule to various elements of society, reserving the most critical functions for our own central government, we expect to see increased public satisfaction and all the benefits which come with it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Industrialist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Industrialist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Industrialist governments seek to maximize industrial capacity by rewarding citizens based entirely on their productivity. From top to bottom, society is organized to encourage hard work and not having fun.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Mercantile Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Mercantile Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Mercantilists seek to ensure their civilization's prosperity through trade, via careful negotiations, brutally unfair tariff, and outright espionage.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Technologist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Technologist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Any time two civilizations have met the less technologically advanced one has come out worse from the encounter. Technologists dedicate all governmental resources to ensure that they never become that dumber civilization.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarDemocracyTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Democracy</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarDemocracyTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Interstellar Democracy form of government, and increases our Administrative capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarDemocracyTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>A system which lets people pick their own rulers, or at least think they're picking their own rulers, has obvious merits in terms of approval and productivity, although adapting it to a civilization this big has proven challenging.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery1_Name</Label>
    <String>War Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of War Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Whether it's because they consider all other civilizations to be inferior, or simply terrifying, members of the War Party are willing to put their entire civilization on a military footing to do something about it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery2_Name</Label>
    <String>Pacifist Party</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Pacifist Party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Pacifist governments forego the language of aggression and militarization and focus all their efforts on promoting culture and social welfare. This makes them well liked in the galactic community, and their words travel far.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStarFederationTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Star Federation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStarFederationTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows use of Star Federation form of government, and increases our Administrative capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStarFederationTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The ultimate in space based governance, an ideal blend of all the freedoms, responsibilities, and delicious seasonings which make up an ideal civic life.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomacyTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Diplomacy</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomacyTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of embassies and the formation of basic treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomacyTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The profit potential an alliance with our neighbors offers is something we should always consider. And failing that, the cost of talking with them will be a fraction of the cost of going to war with then.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Economic Treaty</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of economic treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Economic treaties will lower tariffs and other obstacles that discourage business activities. When well designed, these treaties should result in increased wealth for both parties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Treaty</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of cultural treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>By increasing the interchange of cultural products and making it easier for civilians to cross borders, we can hope to increase the influence we have on our neighbors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Research Treaty</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of research treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By entering into formal information sharing agreements with other civilizations, our researchers can more easily accumulate the masses of data which modern research often requires.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarAlliances_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Alliances</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarAlliances_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved diplomatic buildings. Increases Diplomacy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarAlliances_Dec</Label>
    <String>Turning a friendly species into a formal ally is a supremely delicate process. There's only one way these talks can go right, and a thousand ways they can go wrong. The etiquette of alien handshakes alone is fraught with peril.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Military Alliance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of military alliances.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Formal military alliances will make a war with humanity that much more imposing to our foes. The trade-off is that we risk being drawn into wars not of our choosing. Friends are cheap to have, but allies can be very expensive indeed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Technological Alliance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of technological alliances.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>A technological alliance will dramatically ramp up the research sharing programs we have with our ally. This is valuable information, so we must be sure of their friendship before entering such an agreement.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Alliance</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of cultural alliances.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>A formal cultural alliance will lower almost all barriers to the movement of people and ideas across borders with our neighbor. Not only will this bring us closer, we can hope to have a bigger influence on our neighbor's culture.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEminenceTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Eminence</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEminenceTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced diplomatic buildings. Increases Diplomacy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEminenceTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>A civilization which takes diplomacy seriously and has a long record of fair-minded dealing will always carry a greater voice at the bargaining table. Our people are building that reputation now, and are stronger for it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMajestyTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Majesty</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMajestyTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows formation of assimilation treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMajestyTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>The galaxy wants to believe every word we say. So sterling is our reputation, that our diplomats often find whole worlds begging to join our culture. The pen hasn't just beaten the sword; it's humiliated it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsLobbyist_Name</Label>
    <String>United Planets Lobbyist</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsLobbyist_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks additional Resolutions to be proposed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsLobbyist_Dec</Label>
    <String>There's a shocking amount of backroom dealing which goes on behind the surface of the United Planets. But that's how the sausage is made, and we'll do well if we're better at it than our enemies. And our allies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsClout_Name</Label>
    <String>United Planets Clout</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsClout_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks more powerful Resolutions to be proposed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericUnitedPlanetsClout_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our allies have long been convinced of the benefits of our friendship. Now they see the benefit of our wisdom and leadership. We can no rely on their unwavering support on all United Planets matters.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalInfluence_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Influence</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalInfluence_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic cultural buildings. Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalInfluence_Dec</Label>
    <String>A strong cultural presence, on our worlds and our neighbors' has tremendous long term potential. It lacks some of the visceral appeal of a new type of mass driver, but may in the long run be far more effective at securing humanity's future.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Passionate Representation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>Now that our culture has made inroads on the planets of our neighbors, we can help cement this influence by encouraging our biggest stars to regularly visit and vacation there, serving as ambassadors for our way of life.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Efficient Representation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces cost of cultural buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>Although artists and designers aren't naturally inclined towards thinking about money, after we locked a few of them in a room with an accountant for a bit, they managed to find a number of ways they could do their work more efficiently.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Self Sufficient Representation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Reduces maintenance costs of cultural buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our cultural facilities cost real money to maintain. By encouraging our artists and directors to reuse materials, props, and punch lines whenever possible, we can reduce the ongoing costs of running these enterprises.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOutreach_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Outreach</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOutreach_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved cultural buildings. Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOutreach_Dec</Label>
    <String>By building facilities that focus on spreading our cultural accomplishments amongst our civilians and neighbors, we expect to see even more influence in this region of space, or at the very least, more awards from the artistic community.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Research-Focused Culture</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Influence on research planets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By adapting our cultural products to cast scientists and researchers in a more favorable light, we might find appreciative audiences among research communities.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Approval-Focused Culture</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Influence on planets with high approval.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>A culture which focuses on its leaders is a fine thing to have when those leaders are doing a good job. When the leaders aren't doing a good job, it's filled with harsh satire and unflattering impressions, so watch out for that.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Wealth-Focused Culture</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Influence on wealthy planets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>If people have money, let's not make them ashamed of it. By encouraging displays of conspicuous consumption and a culture which celebrates wealth, we can gain a great deal of influence with people living the good life.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarEmigration_Name</Label>
    <String>Stellar Emigration</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarEmigration_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced cultural buildings. Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericStellarEmigration_Dec</Label>
    <String>Humans are admired throughout the galaxy, reflecting the success of our civilization. If we can make the process of emigration easier, we can spread our influence wider still.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAssimilation_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Assimilation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAssimilation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic cultural buildings. Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAssimilation_Dec</Label>
    <String>Foreign cultures have such backwards ideas that we'll find great value in quickly assimilating and removing the cultural trappings of new arrivals. By doing so can increase the penetration and acceptance of our culture more still.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalDomination_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Domination</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalDomination_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate cultural buildings. Increases Influence.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalDomination_Dec</Label>
    <String>There is no other culture in the galaxy but ours, and anyone who claims otherwise is a heretic. Or just dumb. All sane beings will soon bow down before our celebrities and thinkers.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAffinity_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Affinity</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAffinity_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Prepares civilization for Ascension.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalAffinity_Dec</Label>
    <String>Other universes deserve the benefit of humanity's wisdom and culture. Indeed, it's a bit offensive that they don't see it already. Our thinkers are now beginning to prepare plans for shining our light on the next world, and beyond.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalOutreach_Name</Label>
    <String>Technological Outreach</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalOutreach_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Greatly Increases the spread of our colonies Influence for 15 Turns. (Capstone)</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalOutreach_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our researchers have been instructed to bend those giant brains of Thiers toward finding ways to reach out to the scientist and researchers of other races, and find ways to convince them our way of doing things is the best way to insure technological advancement for the galaxy as a whole. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoCommerce_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Commerce</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoCommerce_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic economic buildings and freighters.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoCommerce_Dec</Label>
    <String>An economy which spans the stars is a pretty complicated beast. We don't need to understand it all of course, just supply the facilities and light regulations for the free market to get to work doing what it does best.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Wealthy Population</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases wealth.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>With targeted tax rates, we can encourage a number of different areas of our economy. A tax policy which favors business and investment should ultimately lead to a wealthier economy for example. Unless the businesses and investors were lying to us.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Supportive Population</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases approval.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>By targeting economic policy to support workers and the civilian population in general, we can ensure we have a much broader base of approval to build our civilization on.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization3_Name</Label>
    <String>Designated Trading Partner</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Adds trade route.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Encouraging and supporting trade is a great way to both bring in extra income and forge closer ties with our neighbors. Everyone's happy when they're making money.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEconomics_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Economics</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEconomics_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved economic buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEconomics_Dec</Label>
    <String>The sheer distance between buyers and sellers in this economy has resulted in us having to rewrite a number of different theories of economics. At minimum, some new banking and economic structures will be required to deal with all the complications.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarBanking_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Banking</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarBanking_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced economic buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarBanking_Dec</Label>
    <String>Capital can now be transferred instantaneously. This has allowed a variety of creative arbitrage opportunities, which will require new regulations and banking theory to contain.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Economy</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases trade route income.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>An economy which prioritizes external trading will be well suited to exploit the wealth of the greater galactic community, or just exploit the greater galactic community in general.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Well Crafted Treaties</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases Diplomatic trade income</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>There is a certain art in the framing of a treaty, and even in an agreement between equals, one party can be more equal than the other. Let's be that more equal party.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Tourism Board</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases tourism income.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>By reducing the obstacles that foreign tourists might face when trying to visit us, we can encourage more of them to travel here and more of their money to stay here.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFinancialSectorsTech_Name</Label>
    <String>Financial Sectors</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFinancialSectorsTech_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic economic buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFinancialSectorsTech_Dec</Label>
    <String>Dedicated financial sectors should help facilitate the flow of capital across our civilization, which will result in more things being built in the places they need to. Wealth creation, in other words, which we can tap for a variety of purposes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticStockMarket_Name</Label>
    <String>Galactic Stock Market</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticStockMarket_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of the ultimate economic buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticStockMarket_Dec</Label>
    <String>Stock exchanges have proven remarkably elusive to establish in this galaxy, and only the most recent advances in communications technology and regulatory capability have made them possible.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicStudy_Name</Label>
    <String>Economic Study</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicStudy_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Substantially boost our civilization's Wealth for 15 Turns. (Capstone)</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicStudy_Dec</Label>
    <String>It's seems for the right price we have been able to incentivize our researchers to focus on assorted ways to boost our colonies Wealth. Unfortunately we will not be able to keep this up to long, or they will all realize they can make much better livings in the private sector. </String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTrade_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Trade</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTrade_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic trading buildings. Adds two trade routes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTrade_Dec</Label>
    <String> Exchanging goods with our neighbors will theoretically enrich us both, and is worth pursuing for that reason alone. Also, if we play it smart, it can enrich us a lot more than the other guy.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization1_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Route  Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases overall value of trade routes</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By optimizing both the outgoing and receiving ends of our trade routes we have been able to achieve a modest overall profit for everyone involved.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization2_Name</Label>
    <String>Expanded Trade</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the establishment of one additional trade route.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We believe the best way to increase trade income is the establish more trade routes. With a bit of effort we have been able to stretch our recourses enough to establish one more.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticTrade_Name</Label>
    <String>Galactic Trade</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticTrade_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved trading buildings. Adds two trade routes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticTrade_Dec</Label>
    <String>By establishing fixed trading hubs and encouraging the markets which develop around them, the wealth of the entire galactic community will flow through our hands. Our ever so slightly sticky hands.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Tariffs</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increases overall value of trade routes</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>By establishing a trade tariffs on our colonies we have been able to increase our trade route profits substantially.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Route Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows the establishment of one additional trade route</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>More trade routes, more trade income, who no need for Tariffs, or 'Luxury items', Some times its best to stick to the basics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticFacilitation_Name</Label>
    <String>Galactic Facilitation</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticFacilitation_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced trading buildings. Adds two trade routes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGalacticFacilitation_Dec</Label>
    <String>The sheer volume of goods that pass through a trading port is staggering, and we'll need new facilities to manage the flow of goods smoothly. And safely. We've had a few too many large masses make dock workers very, very flat.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeMasters_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Masters</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeMasters_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of exotic trading buildings. Adds two trade routes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeMasters_Dec</Label>
    <String>Our civilization is synonymous with wealth and trading, and all intelligent beings know our markets are the only viable place to show their goods. And of course certain advantages accrue to the owners of such a monopoly.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEntertainment_Name</Label>
    <String>Xeno Entertainment</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEntertainment_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of basic entertainment buildings. Increases Approval.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericXenoEntertainment_Dec</Label>
    <String>Without the approval of our people, we won't be able to accomplish very much. Distracting them with various amusements is perhaps a cynical ploy, but it might be easier than trying to treat them as the rational beings they're so often not.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTourism_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Tourism</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTourism_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of improved entertainment buildings. Begin collecting tourism income.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarTourism_Dec</Label>
    <String>Not only can we distract our own citizens with amusements, we can begin luring friendly visitors from our galactic neighbors. This will not only help improve relations, it should result in extra income for us.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationDiversion_Name</Label>
    <String>Population Diversion</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationDiversion_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Allows construction of advanced entertainment buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPopulationDiversion_Dec</Label>
    <String>More amusements! Bigger amusements! Human beings are dreadfully simple sometimes, which is distressing on some level, even if it does make them pretty easy to manage.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus1_Name</Label>
    <String>Easy to Please</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus1_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Increase the morale of your colonies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus1_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have discovered that we can make people feel more confident and happy. With proper messaging, we can keep our citizens happy without all that costly infrastructure.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus2_Name</Label>
    <String>Easily Distracted</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus2_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Makes building Entertainment Improvements much cheaper.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus2_Dec</Label>
    <String>We have discovered that our efforts in keeping our people distracted have paid off. We can now build anything, and they will think it is fun.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus3_Name</Label>
    <String>Eager to Please</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus3_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Greatly reduces the Maintenance required by Entertainment Improvements.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus3_Dec</Label>
    <String>Not only are our people easier to please, they will now do most of the work it takes to distract themselves, for free.</String>
  </StringTable>
 
<!-- Specialization Names and Descriptions -->
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Industrial Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves colonial buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>It only took a few horrific accidents for us to finally come to grips with the challenges of off-world industry, and now that we have, we've identified a number of ways we can begin improving and specializing our industrial capacity.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Construction Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves manufacturing buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericConstructionOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Seemingly small improvements can have a big effect when applied to large projects, and we're working on some very large projects now indeed.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Manufacturing Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves manufacturing buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericManufacturingFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>There's no getting around it: "Incremental improvements in manufacturing techniques" isn't much of a headline. Which is a shame, considering the benefit we expect to see from them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Industrial Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves manufacturing buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIndustrialMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>If it can be dreamed up, we can build it. Indeed, many of our economists now believe that the limiting factor of our industrial capacity is our own imaginations.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Research Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves research buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericResearchOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Researchers are great at inventing things, but surprisingly bad at the business of inventing things. A number of inefficient research practices have developed which we really need to improve upon.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Technological Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves research buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTechnologicalFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>The lab equipment needed to research some of these new fields is incredibly expensive and esoteric. Specializing our research efforts may be necessary to make the most rapid advances.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Planetary Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves farms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPlanetarySpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We've made great strides with our colonization techniques in the past few years, and can now begin considering specific areas we'd like to improve upon.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultural Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves farms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Optimizing our farming processes will lead to a number of benefits which will help our civilization for a very long time. Until people stop needing food, really.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Farming Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves farms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericFarmingFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Although all this attention we pay to improving our farming techniques sometimes make our farmers uncomfortable - they do get set in their ways - the improvements to our food production capacity are too great to ignore.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Agricultural Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves farms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAgriculturalMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our farms now provide an almost unlimited bounty, the food doing much of the hard work itself. Admittedly, the first time you see a plant or animal self-harvest is a little grim, and school field trips have certainly gotten a lot harder.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Colonization Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves potential of extreme worlds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericColonizationFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Mastering living on an extreme world will make life there a lot more tolerable for the poor fools who volunteered for it.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection_Name</Label>
    <String>Biosphere Perfection</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves potential of extreme worlds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBiospherePerfection_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>No longer must our colonists die without cause. Even the deadliest of planets are now perfectly surviable to us.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Interstellar Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves ship systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInterstellarSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we have a bit of experience sending ships out into the darkness and having most of them come back, we've come up with a number of ways to improve our equipment and navigational techniques.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Ion Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericIonOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we've seen them in wide-scale use, we've identified a number of ways we can make our new Ion Drive systems more efficient.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Warp Field Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarpFieldFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Warp field technology is incredibly complicated, and has in more than a few cases, caused a researcher's brains to melt a little bit. But now that we have some experience working with them, we've identified a number of ways to improve their design.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Hyperwarp Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves drives.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHyperwarpMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our ships are already the fastest in the galaxy, our engineers heralded as heroes wherever they go. Fortunately for us, they don't like going out much, instead preferring to keep looking for more improvements to make to their precious engines.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>A concentrated effort to optimize our sensor systems could lead to a number of different improvements or efficiencies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Energy Field Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEnergyFieldFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>As is usually the case when equipment is sent to the field, the technicians who actually use our sensors soon came up with a number of different ways to improve their efficiency and effectiveness.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Sensor Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves sensors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSensorMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We don't anticipate any further increases in the viewing range of our sensors, not until we leave this universe for another one. But we can certainly make them a little more efficient.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Precursor Relic Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves Precursor relic benefits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPrecursorRelicFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Having captured a few Precursor relics and observed the impact they have on our research and culture, we can now try adjusting our Precursor studies to benefit specific areas of our civilization.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Life Support Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Everyone in the navy is very excited that we're trying to optimize our life support systems, and would certainly cheer if they weren't conserving their air.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Support Field Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericSupportFieldFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our early attempts at building field-based life support systems left behind many messes and many possible opportunities for improvement, which we're starting to identify now. Cleaning up the messes: that was the obvious one.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Life Support Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves life support systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLifeSupportMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We have all but mastered direct-nutrient injection technologies, and now have left but a few additional efficiencies to wring out of these systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Orbital Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we've watched a few construction projects accidentally collapse on themselves, we've identified a number of possible improvements we can make to our orbital construction techniques.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Zero Gravity Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericZeroGravityOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We took a big step forward with our most recent adoption of true zero-gravity construction practices. Now, after a few trial runs and one teensy little accident, our engineers have identified further areas for improvement.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Orbital Construction Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericOrbitalConstructionFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We're getting better and better at large scale construction with every passing day, and a number of more efficient design practices are beginning to show up on our engineers' drawing tables. Along with the offensive doodles which have always been there.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Hull Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves hulls.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHullMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We're still finding ways to improve our shipyards, even though they're already the envy of the civilized galaxy. In the uncivilized galaxy they're a bit less envied, but we've never gotten along with those guys anyways.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Carrier Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves carriers.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCarrierFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>There's nothing like doing something a few times to see how terrible you are at it. After a few hilarious mishaps, we've identified a few ways we can improve our carrier operations.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Logistical Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves logistics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericLogisticalOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>A new generation of space accountants are becoming trained as we speak, capable of improving logistical efficiencies most people would be too bored to ever notice.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Weapons Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves weapon systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWeaponsSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>By dedicating their efforts on a specific field of weapons technology, our researchers believe they can deliver a number of more efficient weapon systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Weapon Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Weapons researchers have to keep paces with advances in many other fields to get the most out of their inventions. Right now, recent advances in material sciences are opening the door to a new generation of more efficient weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>High Energy Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericHighEnergyFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>A careful analysis of data returned from the field has revealed a number of inefficiencies which we can begin addressing in the next generation of our beam systems. We may also finally be able to get rid of that funny smell they make.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Beam Weapon Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves beam weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBeamWeaponMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our beam weapons are now absurdly powerful, a terror for anyone foolish enough to get on humanity's wrong side. And yet still our weapon scientists find ways to do better.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Missile Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericMissileOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>After blowing up several thousand target drones and one unfortunate asteroid, our weapons engineers have come up with a number of possible improvements we can implement for our missile platforms.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Warhead Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericWarheadFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We've spent comparatively little research time on the warhead components of our missile systems, but now that we've turned our attention to the matter, a number of possible efficiencies should be achievable with a little effort.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Payload Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves missile weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPayloadMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Various physical limits of this particular universe prevent us from wringing more destructive potential out of this generation of warheads. But we can certainly make them cheaper and lighter.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Some modest improvements in the energy delivery systems of our kinetic weapons could result in improvements to the cost, mass, or range of each unit.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Acceleration Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticAccelerationFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Recent advances in superconducting technology should lead to improvements in the critical energy delivery systems of our kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Kinetic Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves kinetic weapons.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericKineticMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>After several generations of whipping things at other things as fast as possible, our scientists are now really quite good at it. There remain but a few small efficiencies to wring out of the field.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Invasion Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks advanced invasion tactics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericInvasionOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Good news! We've developed some new, possibly amoral, certainly effective techniques for pacifying enemy ground forces.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Gravitational Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks advanced invasion tactics.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericGravitationalFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our ability to manipulate gravitational fields presents several unique tactical possibilities for our ground forces. These are powerful weapons we're giving to guys with pretty thick skulls, so we should definitely remember to keep an eye on them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Defensive Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves defensive systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDefensiveSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>After studying the wreckage of a few vessels we've lost in combat, our engineers have come up with a number of possible improvements we can make to our defensive technologies.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We've received quite a bit of useful data on real world performance of our shield systems, and have devised several possible improvements we can begin making to them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Barrier System Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericBarrierSystemFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>A careful design review of our initial implementation of the Barrier Field system has revealed a number of possible avenues for further improvements. Who says design reviews are unexciting?</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Shield Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves shield systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericShieldMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our shielding technology approaches perfection, our engineers pushing the capabilities of our shield systems right to their theoretical limits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Point Defense Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPointDefenseOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Optimizing our point defense systems should lead to a number of different performance gains. Like possibly less exploded ships.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Counter Measure Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCounterMeasureFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we have some field data on ECM suite performance, we've identified a number of different ways we can improve upon the design and construction of those systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Drone System Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves point defense systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDroneSystemMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Drone systems dramatically increased the sheer volume of our point defense capabilities, so any small improvement in their design should lead to significant cost or weight savings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>We've blown up lots and lots of slabs of armor on the test range, and have come up with a few possible improvements we could make to our armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our armor systems have increased significantly in complexity, and our efforts to model their behavior under impact is only now catching up. This research should help lead to more effective or efficient designs.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Armor Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericArmorMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our mastery of hardening techniques is almost complete, and the galaxy trembles at the girth of our vessels. But even perfection can be improved upon it seems. Some more effort should lead to cheaper or more efficient armor systems.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Diplomatic Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves diplomatic effects.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>The words we use have a limited ability to affect the way we think, and by studying the vocabulary used by our neighbors, we may unlock valuable insights into their mindsets. And possibly even find out how to manipulate them.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Political Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks political parties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>There are several broad ways to organize the government of a space faring civilization, all of which pose distinct advantages and disadvantages. Rest assured, there's no right choice here; regardless of what we pick, everyone will tell us that we made the wrong choice.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Political Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks political parties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>As we continue to manage, and often mis-manage, our affairs, it's become clear that a number of political theories we'd never previously considered viable might actually be very practical when practiced on a galactic scale.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery_Name</Label>
    <String>Political Mastery</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks political parties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericPoliticalMastery_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Coordinating the direction of an entire galactic civilization is tremendously difficult. But thanks to advances in deceit and brain injection technology, we can now put this whole show entirely on a war footing, or, if we choose, the exact opposite.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Diplomatic Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks advanced treaties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericDiplomaticOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Depending on the current state of our civilization, we profit more from some types of treaties than others, and should begin slanting our diplomatic posture in those directions right away.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Alliance Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks advanced alliances.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericAllianceFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Alliances come in a variety of flavors, some of which may be more advantageous to us than others. We should consider our civilization's priorities - and what our new ally is actually good for - before entering such talks.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Improves cultural buildings.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Although the artists responsible for our cultural delivery vehicles like the extra funding we shovel in their direction, few appreciate the suggestion that they could possibly do things more efficiently. They can though. A lot.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Cultural Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Increases influence on specific worlds.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCulturalFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Few works of art and cultural artifacts have broad appeal, and it's often necessary to target one's audience to some extent. By fine tuning the tone and content of our cultural products, we might appeal to demographics which are particularly valuable to us.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization_Name</Label>
    <String>Commerce Specialization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Increases economic benefits.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericCommerceSpecialization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>With a bit of experience managing and regulating markets on a massive scale, we're now able to target specific economic improvements we might like to see.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Economic Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Increases income.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericEconomicFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we have a better understanding of the quirks of galactic scale economies, we can begin trimming back the regulations and policies that seem to be causing inefficiencies in specific industries and areas.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Optimization</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization_Dec</Label>
    <String>Increases trade income.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeOptimization_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Trading is as much an art as a science, but by inducing our traders to use just a smidge more science, they might be able to maximize their profits when dealing with certain counterparties.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Trade Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Unlocks advanced trade routes.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericTradeFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Now that we have a reputation as fair dealers and market makers, it should be possible to target our trading activities to encourage specific economic sectors.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus_Name</Label>
    <String>Approval Focus</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus_Dec</Label>
    <String>Increases approval on specific planets.</String>
  </StringTable>
  <StringTable>
    <Label>GenericApprovalFocus_ShortDec</Label>
    <String>Our cultural engineers inform us that some well planned manipulations of our cultural materials could make our people happier with what they already have. Which seems too good of an opportunity to pass up.</String>
  </StringTable>
 
</StringTableList>
